<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<?metadataRepository version='1.1.0'?>
<repository name='update site: http://www.pramati.com/downloads/eclipse/updates/' type='org.eclipse.equinox.internal.p2.metadata.repository.LocalMetadataRepository' version='1'>
  <properties size='2'>
    <property name='p2.timestamp' value='1480814474786'/>
    <property name='site.checksum' value='2965430523'/>
  </properties>
  <units size='13'>
    <unit id='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.jar' version='1.0.1'>
      <properties size='4'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='com.pramati.eclipse.feature'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='[Enter Feature Description here.]'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description.url' value='http://www.pramati.com/description'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='Pramati'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.jar' version='1.0.1'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='feature' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.update.feature' name='com.pramati.eclipse.feature' version='1.0.1'/>
      </provides>
      <filter>
        (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
      </filter>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='org.eclipse.update.feature' id='com.pramati.eclipse.feature' version='1.0.1'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='http://www.pramati.com/license' url='http://www.pramati.com/license'>
          []
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright uri='http://www.pramati.com/copyright' url='http://www.pramati.com/copyright'>
        [Enter Copyright Description here.]
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.jar' version='2.0.0'>
      <properties size='8'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%featureName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='%description'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%providerName'/>
        <property name='df_LT.license' value='PRAMATI SOFTWARE END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;THIS IS A LICENSE AND NOT A SALE&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;This License Agreement (&quot;Agreement&quot;) is a legal agreement between Pramati Technologies (P) Ltd. (&quot;Pramati&quot;)&#xA;and the end user licensing the Software and Documentation under this Agreement (&quot;Licensee&quot;). By installing&#xA;the Pramati Server, Pramati Message Server (&quot;Server Software&quot;) and/or Pramati Studio (&quot;Studio Software&quot;) &#xA;and/or Pramati Server Plug-in (&quot;Plugin Software&quot;) (collectively &quot;Software&quot;) Licensee agrees to be bound by the &#xA;terms and conditions set forth in this Agreement. In the event Licensee does not wish to be bound to the terms &#xA;of this Agreement, Licensee must promptly return the Software and Documentation to Pramati together with&#xA;proof of purchase in the manner set forth in Pramati&apos;s return policy found on www.pramati.com in order to &#xA;receive a full refund. All returns must comply.  This Agreement applies to any subsequent purchases of the &#xA;Software or Documentation. Licensee must notify all Named Users of the Software of the terms and conditions &#xA;of this Agreement. The Software is licensed to Licensee, not sold.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;LICENSEE MAY USE THE ENCLOSED SOFTWARE AND DOCUMENTATION ONLY IN ACCORDANCE &#xA;WITH THIS AGREEMENT (UNLESS LICENSEE HAS ALREADY SIGNED A VALID LICENSE AGREEMENT&#xA;WITH PRAMATI OR ONE OF ITS SUBSIDIARIES TO USE THE SOFTWARE).&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.&#x9;LICENSE TERMS. Pramati grants to Licensee, and Licensee accepts from Pramati, a limited non-exclusive&#xA;license to install and use the Software and Documentation in accordance with the applicable License Type set&#xA;forth in Section 1.3, below. All rights not specifically granted to Licensee in this Agreement are retained by&#xA;Pramati and its licensors. Licensee shall not allow the use of the Software except on equipment owned or&#xA;leased by Licensee for Licensee&apos;s business purposes and only by the number of authorized users, as&#xA;applicable for the License Type. Licensee shall not allow the unauthorized use of the Software and&#xA;Documentation and will notify Pramati and pay any additional fees pursuant to Pramati&apos;s then current price list&#xA;before making expanded use of the Software.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.1&#x9;License Key. Pramati provides you with a license key which will give you access to the Software in&#xA;accordance with the applicable License Type Licensee has ordered (&quot;License Key&quot;). Licensee will only receive&#xA;a License Key for an Evaluation License, should Licensee wish to purchase a license after the evaluation&#xA;period Pramati will then provide Licensee with the appropriate License Certificate. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.2&#x9;In addition, Pramati will provide Licensee with a certificate of use, except in the case of an Evaluation&#xA;License or a Development License, which sets forth with specificity the licenses granted to you under this&#xA;Agreement (&quot;License Certificate&quot;). The License Certificate is either sent with this Agreement, or separately by&#xA;electronic mail, or when Licensee downloads the Evaluation License or Developer License and is incorporated&#xA;by reference into this Agreement. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3&#x9;&quot;License Type&quot; for Software shall mean any one of the purposes set forth below for which the Software&#xA;(whether Server Software or Studio Software or Plugin Software, as applicable) has been licensed under this&#xA;Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.1&#x9;&quot;Evaluation License&quot; grants Licensee a thirty (30) day, restricted non-exclusive license to install and use&#xA;the Software subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement. Licensee agrees to use the Software&#xA;under such license solely for evaluation purposes. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.2&#x9;&quot;Deployment License&quot; grants Licensee a non-exclusive license to install and use the Software, limited&#xA;only by the Edition and number of CPUs set forth in the License Certificate for deployment with an unlimited&#xA;number of Licensee&apos;s applications subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.3&#x9;&quot;Production License&quot; grants Licensee a non-exclusive license to install and use the Studio Software,&#xA;limited only by number of Named Users set forth in the License Certificate subject to the terms and provisions&#xA;of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.4&#x9;&quot;Development License&quot; grants Licensee a one hundred eighty (180) day, restricted non-exclusive license&#xA;for the number of developers in Licensee&apos;s organization set forth in the License Certificate to install and use&#xA;the Software solely for Licensee&apos;s internal software application development purposes only and not for any&#xA;other purpose subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement. Licensee may use the media on which&#xA;the Software resides to copy the Software onto those computing devices used by Named Users. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.5&#x9;&quot;Limited License&quot; grants Licensee a restricted non-exclusive license to install and use the Software,&#xA;limited by the Edition and number of CPUs set forth in the License Certificate. Licensee may install and use&#xA;Software for deployment of only a specific named Application developed by Application Provider as set forth in&#xA;the License Certificate subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.6&#x9;&quot;Education License&quot; grants Licensee a one hundred eighty (180) day restricted non-exclusive license to&#xA;install and use the Software, limited by the Edition and restricted by the number of Named Users as set forth in&#xA;the License Certificate solely for the purposes of education, training or academic research subject to the terms&#xA;and provisions of this Agreement. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;2. FEES AND PAYMENT. This is a fee bearing license, Pramati&apos;s current license fees are listed at&#xA;www.pramati.com, All fees resulting from this Agreement are due and payable on Licensee&apos;s receipt of the&#xA;invoice if related to a product or Support Service(s) (as defined in Section 3 below) acquired directly from&#xA;Pramati; otherwise such fees are due and payable in accordance with the applicable authorized reseller&apos;s&#xA;policies. Licensee shall pay all applicable shipping charges, and sales, use, value-added, personal property,&#xA;consumption or similar taxes, tariffs or governmental charges, exclusive of Pramati&apos;s or its reseller&apos;s net&#xA;income and corporate franchise taxes.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;3. SUPPORT SERVICES. Licensee may purchase technical telephone support, update assurance and/or&#xA;training services in support of the Software (&quot;Support Service(s)&quot;) pursuant to a separate support agreement&#xA;and in accordance with then-current plans for such Support Service(s), current versions of which can be found&#xA;within Pramati&apos;s website at &quot;www.pramati.com&quot;. Upgrades will be distributed to Licensee in accordance with&#xA;Pramati&apos;s then current maintenance and support fees, terms and conditions.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;4. RESTRICTIONS AND OTHER CONDITIONS.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(a)&#x9;Except as set forth in Section 4(e) below, Licensee may not copy the Software or Documentation.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(b)&#x9;Licensee may not modify, enhance, reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble, supplement, create&#xA;derivative work from, adapt, translate or otherwise reduce the Software to human readable form (except as&#xA;specifically permitted in the Documentation). Notwithstanding the foregoing, in the event Licensee is located in&#xA;the European Economic Area and there is a legal requirement in this area to have access to the source code&#xA;of the Software to achieve interoperability of the Software with other software, Licensee shall notify Pramati&#xA;and Pramati can at its sole option choose to either (i) perform the work in order to achieve such interoperability&#xA;at its then-standard rates for such work to Licensee or (ii) to permit Licensee to reverse engineer parts of the&#xA;Software in order to obtain such source code, but only to the extent necessary to achieve such interoperability.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(c)&#x9;Licensee may not rent or lease the Software to third parties, nor allow use of the Software for service&#xA;bureau, timesharing, application service provider or any other form of shared use.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(d)&#x9;Except as otherwise expressly permitted in this Agreement, Licensee may not cause or permit the&#xA;disclosure, copying, renting, licensing, sublicensing, leasing, dissemination or other distribution of the&#xA;Software or its Documentation by any means or in any form to any third party including, without limitation, any&#xA;form of distributor or reseller without a signed agreement with Pramati granting such right(s).&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(e)&#x9;Licensee may make one copy of the Software and Documentation solely for archival, emergency back-up,&#xA;or disaster recovery purposes; provided, however, that all copyright and other proprietary notices of Pramati and&#xA;its licensors are reproduced on such copies.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(f)&#x9;Licensee acknowledges that, although the Software media may contain other software products, Licensee is&#xA;hereby licensed to install and use only the Software designated by the License Key and the License&#xA;Certificate provided to Licensee for operation of the Software.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(g)&#x9;The Software may not be transferred, sold, assigned or otherwise conveyed (whether by operation of law&#xA;or otherwise) to another party or outside the country in which it was originally delivered to Licensee without&#xA;Pramati&apos;s prior written consent subject to Licensee&apos;s compliance with all applicable export and re-export&#xA;regulations and restrictions; provided, however, that if Licensee is located in the European Economic Area, and&#xA;is a legal requirement in this area, Licensee may transfer Licensee&apos;s copy of the Software together with its&#xA;Documentation on a permanent basis, so long as Licensee notifies Pramati as to the name and address of the&#xA;recipient of Licensee&apos;s copy and that such recipient agrees in writing to be bound by the terms and conditions&#xA;of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(h)&#x9;Results of benchmark or other performance tests run on the Software may not be disclosed to any third&#xA;party without Pramati&apos;s prior written consent.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(i)&#x9;The Software contains software programs written in Java. The Software is not fault-tolerant and is not&#xA;designed, manufactured or intended for use or resale in the on-line control, design, construction, operation or&#xA;maintenance of any nuclear facilities, aircraft navigation or communication systems, air traffic control, direct&#xA;life support machines, or weapons systems, in which the failure of the Software could lead directly to death,&#xA;personal injury, or severe physical or environmental damage (&quot;High Risk Activities&quot;). Pramati and its suppliers&#xA;specifically disclaim any express or implied warranty of fitness for High Risk Activities. Licensee agrees that it&#xA;is not licensed to use the Software for High Risk Activities and that failure to comply with this section will result&#xA;in immediate termination of this Agreement without refund.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(j)&#x9;Third party software products supplied with the Software are provided to Licensee subject to such third&#xA;party&apos;s license agreement with Pramati, the terms of which may change from time to time. The Cloudscape&#xA;software products may only be used as a part of Pramati&apos;s development Software. The Cloudscape software&#xA;products may only be used on the operating system platforms on which Informix has made the Cloudscape&#xA;software generally commercially available. Licensee may not copy, distribute, or otherwise deploy the&#xA;Cloudscape software products or any other programs developed using such Cloudscape software. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;GENERAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;5. COPYRIGHT AND OWNERSHIP. Title, ownership rights, and all intellectual property rights in and to the&#xA;Software and Documentation including all copies thereof, and all rights therein including, but not limited to, all&#xA;trade secrets, trademarks, patents, copyrights, trade secrets and moral rights shall remain the sole and&#xA;exclusive property of Pramati and/or its licensors. Licensee acknowledges that the Software contains valuable&#xA;confidential information and trade secrets of Pramati and/or its licensors. No title or ownership to the Software&#xA;or Documentation or any part or modification thereof is transferred to Licensee. Software is protected by&#xA;copyright laws and international treaty provisions. Licensee shall not remove or alter Pramati&apos;s or any third&#xA;party&apos; s ownership, trademark, copyright, or other proprietary notices on the Software or Documentation.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;5.1 Pramati acknowledges that Software contains third-party software as listed in the attached files.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;5.2 Licensee acknowledges that Software contains software from third-party and agrees to abide by the&#xA;third-party agreements attached hereto. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;6. U.S. GOVERNMENT RIGHTS. If the Software or its Documentation is acquired by or on behalf of the United&#xA;States Government, the United States Government agrees that such Software and Documentation is&#xA;&quot;commercial computer software&quot; or &quot;commercial computer software documentation&quot; and that use,&#xA;modification, duplication and disclosure of the Software and its Documentation by the United States&#xA;Government is subject to restrictions set forth in this Agreement or in a written agreement to the contrary&#xA;specifying the United States Government&apos;s right to use the Software and its Documentation, pursuant to FAR&#xA;§ 12.212(a) and/or DFARS § 227.7202-1(a), as applicable. Pramati reserves all unpublished rights under U.S.&#xA;copyright laws.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;7. TERM OF LICENSE. Either party may terminate this Agreement if the other party materially breaches any of&#xA;its obligations hereunder and fails to cure such breach within thirty (30) days after written notice. Upon&#xA;termination, all rights granted to Licensee hereunder shall terminate and Licensee shall cease using the&#xA;Software, and within five (5) days of termination Licensee shall destroy or return to Pramati all copies of the&#xA;Software and its Documentation in any form. Upon request, Licensee shall certify that all copies of the&#xA;Software have been destroyed. Termination of this Agreement will not affect any provisions relating to the&#xA;payment of amounts due, limiting or disclaiming Pramati&apos;s liability, confidentiality, and ownership of copyrights&#xA;and other intellectual property of Pramati including, but not limited to, the Software and Documentation, which&#xA;provisions will survive termination of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;8. CONFIDENTIALITY.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;8.1 Definition. Licensee agrees that information disclosed to it by Pramati including, but not limited to,&#xA;information learned or developed using the Software or Documentation, or that relates to its products, designs,&#xA;research, development, know-how, or third party confidential information, will be considered and referred to &#xA;collectively in this Agreement as &quot;Confidential Information.&quot; Confidential Information, however, does not include&#xA;information that 1) is now or subsequently becomes generally available to the public through no fault or breach&#xA;on the part of Licensee; 2) Licensee can demonstrate to have had rightfully in its possession prior to&#xA;disclosure by Pramati of such Confidential Information; 3) is independently developed by Licensee without the&#xA;use of any Confidential Information, the Software or Documentation of Pramati; or 4) Licensee rightfully obtains&#xA;from a third party who has the right to transfer or disclose it.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;8.2 Nondisclosure and Nonuse of Confidential Information. Except as otherwise set forth in this Agreement,&#xA;Licensee agrees that it will not disclosure, publish, or disseminate Confidential Information of Pramati to&#xA;anyone other than those of its employees with a demonstrated need to know, and Licensee agrees to take all&#xA;reasonable precautions to prevent any unauthorized use, disclosure, publication, or dissemination of&#xA;Confidential Information. Licensee agrees to use any Confidential Information disclosed to it solely for the&#xA;purposes contemplated by this Agreement and not otherwise for its own or any third party&apos;s benefit without the&#xA;prior written approval of an authorized representative of Pramati in each instance. All Confidential Information&#xA;remains the property of Pramati. Licensee shall enter into appropriate agreements, if Licensee has not already&#xA;done so, to protect the Confidential Information. Licensee shall not use Confidential Information at any time for&#xA;any purpose other than as authorized by Pramati.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;9. LIMITED WARRANTY. For a period of thirty (30) days from the date of Licensee&apos;s receipt of the Software,&#xA;Pramati warrants that the Software, when properly installed and used with the equipment configuration and in&#xA;the operating environment specified by Pramati, will operate in all material respects in conformity with its&#xA;Documentation, and the Software media shall be free of defects. Pramati warrants that Software telephone&#xA;support and training services (&quot;Related Service(s)&quot;) will be performed by qualified personnel in a professional&#xA;manner. In the event of non-conforming Software or Related Service(s), or if the media is defective, Licensee&apos;s&#xA;sole remedy and Pramati&apos;s exclusive liability shall be, as applicable and at Pramati&apos;s option, replacement of&#xA;the affected Software or media, or re-performance of the Related Service(s) at no additional charge, or a refund&#xA;of the fees paid for the affected Software or Related Service(s). EVALUATION SOFTWARE AND ANY THIRD&#xA;PARTY SOFTWARE ARE PROVIDED TO LICENSEE &quot;AS IS&quot; WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY, EXPRESS OR&#xA;IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE. PRAMATI DISCLAIMS ALL OTHER WARRANTIES AND&#xA;CONDITIONS, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION&#xA;THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND&#xA;WHETHER ARISING BY STATUTE OR IN LAW OR AS A RESULT OF A COURSE OF DEALING OR&#xA;USAGE OF TRADE, WITH RESPECT TO THE SOFTWARE, ITS DOCUMENTATION, SUPPORT OR OTHER&#xA;SERVICES RELATED TO THE SOFTWARE. NO WARRANTY IS MADE REGARDING THE RESULTS OF&#xA;THE SOFTWARE OR RELATED SERVICES OR THAT ALL ERRORS IN THE SOFTWARE WILL BE&#xA;CORRECTED, OR THAT THE SOFTWARE&apos;S FUNCTIONALITY WILL MEET LICENSEE&apos;S REQUIREMENTS.&#xA;LICENSEE ACKNOWLEDGES LICENSEE&apos;S RESPONSIBILITY TO (i) REGULARLY BACK UP DATA&#xA;MAINTAINED ON ANY COMPUTER SYSTEM USING THE SOFTWARE AND (ii) ADEQUATELY TEST&#xA;PRIOR TO DEPLOYMENT EACH PRODUCTION VERSION OF THE SOFTWARE IN A CONFIGURATION&#xA;WHICH REASONABLY SIMULATES LICENSEE&apos;S PLANNED DEPLOYMENT OR PRODUCTION&#xA;ENVIRONMENT. This limited warranty gives Licensee specific legal rights. Licensee may have other rights that&#xA;vary among jurisdictions. Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of implied conditions or warranties,&#xA;statutory or otherwise, so the above exclusions may not apply to Licensee.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;10. LIMITATIONS ON LIABILITY. PRAMATI&apos;S LICENSORS SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR DIRECT DAMAGES&#xA;OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER UNDER THIS AGREEMENT. UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL&#xA;PRAMATI, ITS SUBSIDIARIES OR ANY OF ITS LICENSORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOSS OR&#xA;INACCURACY OF DATA, LOSS OF PROFITS OR INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL&#xA;OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES, EVEN IF SUCH PARTY HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF&#xA;SUCH DAMAGES. TOTAL LIABILITY, IF ANY, ARISING OUT OF THIS AGREEMENT OR LICENSEE&apos;S USE&#xA;OF THE SOFTWARE OR RELATED SERVICES SHALL EXCEED THE FEES PAID BY LICENSEE FOR THE&#xA;AFFECTED SOFTWARE OR RELATED SERVICE(S) GIVING RISE TO THE CLAIM. THE FOREGOING&#xA;RESTRICTIONS, DISCLAIMERS AND LIMITATIONS SHALL REMAIN IN FORCE EVEN IN THE EVENT OF A&#xA;FUNDAMENTAL BREACH BY PRAMATI OR A BREACH BY PRAMATI OF A CONDITION OR&#xA;FUNDAMENTAL TERM HEREUNDER. Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion or limitation of indirect,&#xA;special, incidental, consequential or exemplary damages or the limitation of liability to specified amounts, so&#xA;the above limitations or exclusions may not apply to Licensee. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;10.1 Licensee acknowledges that Pramati has no knowledge of, or control over, the installation or use of the&#xA;Software by Licensee. Licensee agrees to defend, indemnify and hold Pramati harmless with respect to any&#xA;suit, claim or proceeding brought against Pramati alleging that installation or use by, or under authority of,&#xA;Licensee of the Software caused personal injury, property damage, or economic loss.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;11. GOVERNING LAW; COMPLETE AGREEMENT. This Agreement shall be construed and enforced in&#xA;accordance with the laws of the State of California, United States of America. The parties agree that venue for&#xA;any dispute under this Agreement shall be San Mateo County, California, U.S.A.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;12. AUDIT RIGHTS.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;12.1 Licensee shall keep accurate records of all activity with respect to use of the Software by Licensee,&#xA;including, without limitation, all Editions of Software used and the number of Named Users accessing the&#xA;Software or the number of CPUs. Licensee shall provide Pramati with summaries of such records upon&#xA;request. At any time during the term of this Agreement, Pramati shall have the right to audit Licensee&apos;s records&#xA;in order to verify that Licensee is limiting use of the Software in accordance with this Agreement. If any audit&#xA;reveals that Licensee is not limiting use of the Software in accordance with this Agreement, Licensee shall&#xA;pay Pramati any underpaid license fees at Pramati&apos;s then current rates within five days of notification of such&#xA;underpayment. If any audit reveals that Licensee has underpaid Pramati by an amount equal to or greater than&#xA;five percent of applicable license fees, Licensee shall also reimburse Pramati for the costs associated with the&#xA;audit.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;13. NOTICES. All notices or other communications required to be given under this Agreement shall be in&#xA;writing and delivered either personally or by mail via an internationally recognized governmental or private mail&#xA;service, certified, return receipt requested, postage prepaid, and addressed as provided in this Agreement or&#xA;as otherwise requested by the receiving party. Notices delivered personally shall be effective upon delivery and&#xA;notices delivered by mail shall be effective upon their receipt by the party to whom they are addressed.&#xA;Licensee shall address all correspondence regarding this Agreement to the Company Secretary of Pramati&#xA;Technologies (P) Ltd. at the Hyderabad, India Office whose address is available at www.pramati.com.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;14. ENTIRE AGREEMENT; MODIFICATIONS AND WAIVERS. This Agreement constitutes the full and entire&#xA;understanding and agreement between the parties with regard to the subjects hereof.  No term of this&#xA;Agreement may be modified except by a writing signed by an authorized representative of each of the parties.&#xA;A waiver by a party of its rights under this Agreement shall not be binding unless contained in a writing signed&#xA;by an authorized representative of the party waiving its rights. The non-enforcement or waiver of any provision&#xA;on one (1) occasion shall not constitute a waiver of such provision on any other occasions unless expressly so&#xA;agreed in writing. It is agreed that no use of trade or other regular practice or method of dealing between the&#xA;parties hereto shall be used to modify, interpret, supplement, or alter in any manner the terms of this&#xA;Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;15. SEVERABILITY. In the event that any provision of this Agreement is found invalid or unenforceable pursuant&#xA;to judicial decree or decision, the remainder of this Agreement shall remain valid and enforceable according to&#xA;its terms.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;16. FORCE MAJEURE. No party shall be responsible for any failure to perform due to unforeseen&#xA;circumstances or to causes beyond the party&apos;s reasonable control, including but not limited to acts of God,&#xA;war, riot, embargoes, acts of civil or military authorities, fire, floods, accidents, strikes, or shortages of&#xA;transportation, facilities, fuel, energy, labor, or materials. In the event of any such delay, a party may defer any&#xA;delivery dates for a period equal to the time of such delay. Notwithstanding the foregoing, if a party is in default&#xA;under this Section for more than fifteen (15) days, the non-defaulting party may terminate this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;17. ARBITRATION. Any controversy or claim arising out of or relating to this Agreement, or the breach thereof&#xA;shall be settled by binding arbitration in the County of San Mateo, California, administered by the American&#xA;Arbitration Association in accordance with its then current Commercial Arbitration Rules, and judgment on the&#xA;award rendered by the arbitrator may be entered in any court having jurisdiction thereof. The arbitrator may&#xA;award monetary damages, punitive damages, injunctive relief, rescission, restitution, costs and attorneys&apos;&#xA;fees. The arbitration award shall be final and binding regardless of whether one of the parties fails or refuses to&#xA;participate in the arbitration. The arbitrator shall not have the power to amend this Agreement in any respect.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;18. ATTORNEYS&apos; FEES. In the event of any dispute with respect to this Agreement, the prevailing party shall&#xA;be entitled to reasonable attorneys&apos; fees and other costs and expenses incurred in resolving such dispute.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;19. TAXES. Unless otherwise agreed between Consultant and Company, Consultant and Company shall each&#xA;have sole responsibility for collecting, reporting, and/or paying all income, sales, excise, property, value-added&#xA;tax, and other taxes imposed by any governmental authority as they pertain to Consultant&apos;s and Company&apos;s&#xA;respective duties, obligations, and performance hereunder.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20. DEFINITIONS.&#xA;&#xA;As used herein, the terms set forth below shall have the following respective meanings:&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.1 &quot;Documentation&quot; means the publications prepared and delivered to Licensee by Pramati that accompanies&#xA;the Software, such as reference, user, installation, systems administrator and technical guides. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.2 &quot;CPU&quot; means each central processing unit designated for use on a specific computing device.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.3 &quot;Software&quot; shall mean the machine readable object code, delivered by Pramati, to Licensee and may&#xA;include software licensed from third parties, together with other software and/or other products subsequently&#xA;delivered to Licensee by Pramati and all updates and upgrades of the same provided to Licensee by Pramati&#xA;and/or its suppliers. Software includes &quot;Server Software&quot; including current release(s) of Pramati Server and&#xA;Pramati Message Server and &quot;Studio Software&quot; including current release(s) of Pramati Studio and &quot;Plugin&#xA;Software&quot;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.4 &quot;Pramati&quot; shall mean Pramati Technologies (P) Limited, as incorporated in the State of Andhra Pradesh,&#xA;India, under Companies Act, 1956, whose address can be found at Pramati&apos;s website at www.pramati.com.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.5 &quot;Licensee&quot; shall mean the entity or individual, either on the individual&apos; s behalf or on behalf of the entity that&#xA;individual represents, who installs the Software or otherwise agrees to be bound by the terms and conditions&#xA;contained in this Agreement. Further, each individual representing an entity represents and warrants that&#xA;he/she has the authority to bind the entity to this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.6 &quot;Named Users&quot; shall mean an individual or individuals employed by Licensee who is/are authorized to use&#xA;the software. The number of licenses for the Program must equal the total number of Named Users.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.7 &quot;Application&quot; shall mean machine-readable object code provided by &quot;Application Provider&quot; to Licensee&#xA;which may be deployed on Software.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.8 &quot;Edition&quot; shall mean either the Standard Edition or the Enterprise Edition of the Software.  The Standard&#xA;Edition does not allow use of certain features available in the Enterprise Edition.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;BY CLICKING THE &quot;ACCEPT&quot; BUTTON OR CHECKING THE &quot;ACCEPT&quot; CHECK-BOX DURING&#xA;INSTALLATION OF THE SOFTWARE, LICENSEE IS AGREEING TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND&#xA;CONDITIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT.&#xA;'/>
        <property name='df_LT.copyright' value='Copyright © 2008 Pramati Technologies. All Rights Reserved.'/>
        <property name='df_LT.featureName' value='Pramati Server 6.0 Plugin'/>
        <property name='df_LT.description' value='Pramati Server Plugin Feature 2.0.0 : Supported server versions 4.1, 5.0 and 6.0'/>
        <property name='df_LT.providerName' value='Pramati Technologies'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.jar' version='2.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='feature' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.update.feature' name='com.pramati.eclipse.feature' version='2.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <filter>
        (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
      </filter>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='org.eclipse.update.feature' id='com.pramati.eclipse.feature' version='2.0.0'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='%25licenseURL' url='%25licenseURL'>
          %license
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        %copyright
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.jar' version='2.1.0'>
      <properties size='8'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%featureName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='%description'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%providerName'/>
        <property name='df_LT.license' value='PRAMATI SOFTWARE END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;THIS IS A LICENSE AND NOT A SALE&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;This License Agreement (&quot;Agreement&quot;) is a legal agreement between Pramati Technologies (P) Ltd. (&quot;Pramati&quot;)&#xA;and the end user licensing the Software and Documentation under this Agreement (&quot;Licensee&quot;). By installing&#xA;the Pramati Server, Pramati Message Server (&quot;Server Software&quot;) and/or Pramati Studio (&quot;Studio Software&quot;) &#xA;and/or Pramati Server Plug-in (&quot;Plugin Software&quot;) (collectively &quot;Software&quot;) Licensee agrees to be bound by the &#xA;terms and conditions set forth in this Agreement. In the event Licensee does not wish to be bound to the terms &#xA;of this Agreement, Licensee must promptly return the Software and Documentation to Pramati together with&#xA;proof of purchase in the manner set forth in Pramati&apos;s return policy found on www.pramati.com in order to &#xA;receive a full refund. All returns must comply.  This Agreement applies to any subsequent purchases of the &#xA;Software or Documentation. Licensee must notify all Named Users of the Software of the terms and conditions &#xA;of this Agreement. The Software is licensed to Licensee, not sold.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;LICENSEE MAY USE THE ENCLOSED SOFTWARE AND DOCUMENTATION ONLY IN ACCORDANCE &#xA;WITH THIS AGREEMENT (UNLESS LICENSEE HAS ALREADY SIGNED A VALID LICENSE AGREEMENT&#xA;WITH PRAMATI OR ONE OF ITS SUBSIDIARIES TO USE THE SOFTWARE).&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.&#x9;LICENSE TERMS. Pramati grants to Licensee, and Licensee accepts from Pramati, a limited non-exclusive&#xA;license to install and use the Software and Documentation in accordance with the applicable License Type set&#xA;forth in Section 1.3, below. All rights not specifically granted to Licensee in this Agreement are retained by&#xA;Pramati and its licensors. Licensee shall not allow the use of the Software except on equipment owned or&#xA;leased by Licensee for Licensee&apos;s business purposes and only by the number of authorized users, as&#xA;applicable for the License Type. Licensee shall not allow the unauthorized use of the Software and&#xA;Documentation and will notify Pramati and pay any additional fees pursuant to Pramati&apos;s then current price list&#xA;before making expanded use of the Software.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.1&#x9;License Key. Pramati provides you with a license key which will give you access to the Software in&#xA;accordance with the applicable License Type Licensee has ordered (&quot;License Key&quot;). Licensee will only receive&#xA;a License Key for an Evaluation License, should Licensee wish to purchase a license after the evaluation&#xA;period Pramati will then provide Licensee with the appropriate License Certificate. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.2&#x9;In addition, Pramati will provide Licensee with a certificate of use, except in the case of an Evaluation&#xA;License or a Development License, which sets forth with specificity the licenses granted to you under this&#xA;Agreement (&quot;License Certificate&quot;). The License Certificate is either sent with this Agreement, or separately by&#xA;electronic mail, or when Licensee downloads the Evaluation License or Developer License and is incorporated&#xA;by reference into this Agreement. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3&#x9;&quot;License Type&quot; for Software shall mean any one of the purposes set forth below for which the Software&#xA;(whether Server Software or Studio Software or Plugin Software, as applicable) has been licensed under this&#xA;Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.1&#x9;&quot;Evaluation License&quot; grants Licensee a thirty (30) day, restricted non-exclusive license to install and use&#xA;the Software subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement. Licensee agrees to use the Software&#xA;under such license solely for evaluation purposes. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.2&#x9;&quot;Deployment License&quot; grants Licensee a non-exclusive license to install and use the Software, limited&#xA;only by the Edition and number of CPUs set forth in the License Certificate for deployment with an unlimited&#xA;number of Licensee&apos;s applications subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.3&#x9;&quot;Production License&quot; grants Licensee a non-exclusive license to install and use the Studio Software,&#xA;limited only by number of Named Users set forth in the License Certificate subject to the terms and provisions&#xA;of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.4&#x9;&quot;Development License&quot; grants Licensee a one hundred eighty (180) day, restricted non-exclusive license&#xA;for the number of developers in Licensee&apos;s organization set forth in the License Certificate to install and use&#xA;the Software solely for Licensee&apos;s internal software application development purposes only and not for any&#xA;other purpose subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement. Licensee may use the media on which&#xA;the Software resides to copy the Software onto those computing devices used by Named Users. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.5&#x9;&quot;Limited License&quot; grants Licensee a restricted non-exclusive license to install and use the Software,&#xA;limited by the Edition and number of CPUs set forth in the License Certificate. Licensee may install and use&#xA;Software for deployment of only a specific named Application developed by Application Provider as set forth in&#xA;the License Certificate subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.6&#x9;&quot;Education License&quot; grants Licensee a one hundred eighty (180) day restricted non-exclusive license to&#xA;install and use the Software, limited by the Edition and restricted by the number of Named Users as set forth in&#xA;the License Certificate solely for the purposes of education, training or academic research subject to the terms&#xA;and provisions of this Agreement. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;2. FEES AND PAYMENT. This is a fee bearing license, Pramati&apos;s current license fees are listed at&#xA;www.pramati.com, All fees resulting from this Agreement are due and payable on Licensee&apos;s receipt of the&#xA;invoice if related to a product or Support Service(s) (as defined in Section 3 below) acquired directly from&#xA;Pramati; otherwise such fees are due and payable in accordance with the applicable authorized reseller&apos;s&#xA;policies. Licensee shall pay all applicable shipping charges, and sales, use, value-added, personal property,&#xA;consumption or similar taxes, tariffs or governmental charges, exclusive of Pramati&apos;s or its reseller&apos;s net&#xA;income and corporate franchise taxes.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;3. SUPPORT SERVICES. Licensee may purchase technical telephone support, update assurance and/or&#xA;training services in support of the Software (&quot;Support Service(s)&quot;) pursuant to a separate support agreement&#xA;and in accordance with then-current plans for such Support Service(s), current versions of which can be found&#xA;within Pramati&apos;s website at &quot;www.pramati.com&quot;. Upgrades will be distributed to Licensee in accordance with&#xA;Pramati&apos;s then current maintenance and support fees, terms and conditions.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;4. RESTRICTIONS AND OTHER CONDITIONS.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(a)&#x9;Except as set forth in Section 4(e) below, Licensee may not copy the Software or Documentation.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(b)&#x9;Licensee may not modify, enhance, reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble, supplement, create&#xA;derivative work from, adapt, translate or otherwise reduce the Software to human readable form (except as&#xA;specifically permitted in the Documentation). Notwithstanding the foregoing, in the event Licensee is located in&#xA;the European Economic Area and there is a legal requirement in this area to have access to the source code&#xA;of the Software to achieve interoperability of the Software with other software, Licensee shall notify Pramati&#xA;and Pramati can at its sole option choose to either (i) perform the work in order to achieve such interoperability&#xA;at its then-standard rates for such work to Licensee or (ii) to permit Licensee to reverse engineer parts of the&#xA;Software in order to obtain such source code, but only to the extent necessary to achieve such interoperability.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(c)&#x9;Licensee may not rent or lease the Software to third parties, nor allow use of the Software for service&#xA;bureau, timesharing, application service provider or any other form of shared use.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(d)&#x9;Except as otherwise expressly permitted in this Agreement, Licensee may not cause or permit the&#xA;disclosure, copying, renting, licensing, sublicensing, leasing, dissemination or other distribution of the&#xA;Software or its Documentation by any means or in any form to any third party including, without limitation, any&#xA;form of distributor or reseller without a signed agreement with Pramati granting such right(s).&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(e)&#x9;Licensee may make one copy of the Software and Documentation solely for archival, emergency back-up,&#xA;or disaster recovery purposes; provided, however, that all copyright and other proprietary notices of Pramati and&#xA;its licensors are reproduced on such copies.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(f)&#x9;Licensee acknowledges that, although the Software media may contain other software products, Licensee is&#xA;hereby licensed to install and use only the Software designated by the License Key and the License&#xA;Certificate provided to Licensee for operation of the Software.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(g)&#x9;The Software may not be transferred, sold, assigned or otherwise conveyed (whether by operation of law&#xA;or otherwise) to another party or outside the country in which it was originally delivered to Licensee without&#xA;Pramati&apos;s prior written consent subject to Licensee&apos;s compliance with all applicable export and re-export&#xA;regulations and restrictions; provided, however, that if Licensee is located in the European Economic Area, and&#xA;is a legal requirement in this area, Licensee may transfer Licensee&apos;s copy of the Software together with its&#xA;Documentation on a permanent basis, so long as Licensee notifies Pramati as to the name and address of the&#xA;recipient of Licensee&apos;s copy and that such recipient agrees in writing to be bound by the terms and conditions&#xA;of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(h)&#x9;Results of benchmark or other performance tests run on the Software may not be disclosed to any third&#xA;party without Pramati&apos;s prior written consent.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(i)&#x9;The Software contains software programs written in Java. The Software is not fault-tolerant and is not&#xA;designed, manufactured or intended for use or resale in the on-line control, design, construction, operation or&#xA;maintenance of any nuclear facilities, aircraft navigation or communication systems, air traffic control, direct&#xA;life support machines, or weapons systems, in which the failure of the Software could lead directly to death,&#xA;personal injury, or severe physical or environmental damage (&quot;High Risk Activities&quot;). Pramati and its suppliers&#xA;specifically disclaim any express or implied warranty of fitness for High Risk Activities. Licensee agrees that it&#xA;is not licensed to use the Software for High Risk Activities and that failure to comply with this section will result&#xA;in immediate termination of this Agreement without refund.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(j)&#x9;Third party software products supplied with the Software are provided to Licensee subject to such third&#xA;party&apos;s license agreement with Pramati, the terms of which may change from time to time. The Cloudscape&#xA;software products may only be used as a part of Pramati&apos;s development Software. The Cloudscape software&#xA;products may only be used on the operating system platforms on which Informix has made the Cloudscape&#xA;software generally commercially available. Licensee may not copy, distribute, or otherwise deploy the&#xA;Cloudscape software products or any other programs developed using such Cloudscape software. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;GENERAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;5. COPYRIGHT AND OWNERSHIP. Title, ownership rights, and all intellectual property rights in and to the&#xA;Software and Documentation including all copies thereof, and all rights therein including, but not limited to, all&#xA;trade secrets, trademarks, patents, copyrights, trade secrets and moral rights shall remain the sole and&#xA;exclusive property of Pramati and/or its licensors. Licensee acknowledges that the Software contains valuable&#xA;confidential information and trade secrets of Pramati and/or its licensors. No title or ownership to the Software&#xA;or Documentation or any part or modification thereof is transferred to Licensee. Software is protected by&#xA;copyright laws and international treaty provisions. Licensee shall not remove or alter Pramati&apos;s or any third&#xA;party&apos; s ownership, trademark, copyright, or other proprietary notices on the Software or Documentation.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;5.1 Pramati acknowledges that Software contains third-party software as listed in the attached files.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;5.2 Licensee acknowledges that Software contains software from third-party and agrees to abide by the&#xA;third-party agreements attached hereto. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;6. U.S. GOVERNMENT RIGHTS. If the Software or its Documentation is acquired by or on behalf of the United&#xA;States Government, the United States Government agrees that such Software and Documentation is&#xA;&quot;commercial computer software&quot; or &quot;commercial computer software documentation&quot; and that use,&#xA;modification, duplication and disclosure of the Software and its Documentation by the United States&#xA;Government is subject to restrictions set forth in this Agreement or in a written agreement to the contrary&#xA;specifying the United States Government&apos;s right to use the Software and its Documentation, pursuant to FAR&#xA;§ 12.212(a) and/or DFARS § 227.7202-1(a), as applicable. Pramati reserves all unpublished rights under U.S.&#xA;copyright laws.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;7. TERM OF LICENSE. Either party may terminate this Agreement if the other party materially breaches any of&#xA;its obligations hereunder and fails to cure such breach within thirty (30) days after written notice. Upon&#xA;termination, all rights granted to Licensee hereunder shall terminate and Licensee shall cease using the&#xA;Software, and within five (5) days of termination Licensee shall destroy or return to Pramati all copies of the&#xA;Software and its Documentation in any form. Upon request, Licensee shall certify that all copies of the&#xA;Software have been destroyed. Termination of this Agreement will not affect any provisions relating to the&#xA;payment of amounts due, limiting or disclaiming Pramati&apos;s liability, confidentiality, and ownership of copyrights&#xA;and other intellectual property of Pramati including, but not limited to, the Software and Documentation, which&#xA;provisions will survive termination of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;8. CONFIDENTIALITY.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;8.1 Definition. Licensee agrees that information disclosed to it by Pramati including, but not limited to,&#xA;information learned or developed using the Software or Documentation, or that relates to its products, designs,&#xA;research, development, know-how, or third party confidential information, will be considered and referred to &#xA;collectively in this Agreement as &quot;Confidential Information.&quot; Confidential Information, however, does not include&#xA;information that 1) is now or subsequently becomes generally available to the public through no fault or breach&#xA;on the part of Licensee; 2) Licensee can demonstrate to have had rightfully in its possession prior to&#xA;disclosure by Pramati of such Confidential Information; 3) is independently developed by Licensee without the&#xA;use of any Confidential Information, the Software or Documentation of Pramati; or 4) Licensee rightfully obtains&#xA;from a third party who has the right to transfer or disclose it.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;8.2 Nondisclosure and Nonuse of Confidential Information. Except as otherwise set forth in this Agreement,&#xA;Licensee agrees that it will not disclosure, publish, or disseminate Confidential Information of Pramati to&#xA;anyone other than those of its employees with a demonstrated need to know, and Licensee agrees to take all&#xA;reasonable precautions to prevent any unauthorized use, disclosure, publication, or dissemination of&#xA;Confidential Information. Licensee agrees to use any Confidential Information disclosed to it solely for the&#xA;purposes contemplated by this Agreement and not otherwise for its own or any third party&apos;s benefit without the&#xA;prior written approval of an authorized representative of Pramati in each instance. All Confidential Information&#xA;remains the property of Pramati. Licensee shall enter into appropriate agreements, if Licensee has not already&#xA;done so, to protect the Confidential Information. Licensee shall not use Confidential Information at any time for&#xA;any purpose other than as authorized by Pramati.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;9. LIMITED WARRANTY. For a period of thirty (30) days from the date of Licensee&apos;s receipt of the Software,&#xA;Pramati warrants that the Software, when properly installed and used with the equipment configuration and in&#xA;the operating environment specified by Pramati, will operate in all material respects in conformity with its&#xA;Documentation, and the Software media shall be free of defects. Pramati warrants that Software telephone&#xA;support and training services (&quot;Related Service(s)&quot;) will be performed by qualified personnel in a professional&#xA;manner. In the event of non-conforming Software or Related Service(s), or if the media is defective, Licensee&apos;s&#xA;sole remedy and Pramati&apos;s exclusive liability shall be, as applicable and at Pramati&apos;s option, replacement of&#xA;the affected Software or media, or re-performance of the Related Service(s) at no additional charge, or a refund&#xA;of the fees paid for the affected Software or Related Service(s). EVALUATION SOFTWARE AND ANY THIRD&#xA;PARTY SOFTWARE ARE PROVIDED TO LICENSEE &quot;AS IS&quot; WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY, EXPRESS OR&#xA;IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE. PRAMATI DISCLAIMS ALL OTHER WARRANTIES AND&#xA;CONDITIONS, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION&#xA;THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND&#xA;WHETHER ARISING BY STATUTE OR IN LAW OR AS A RESULT OF A COURSE OF DEALING OR&#xA;USAGE OF TRADE, WITH RESPECT TO THE SOFTWARE, ITS DOCUMENTATION, SUPPORT OR OTHER&#xA;SERVICES RELATED TO THE SOFTWARE. NO WARRANTY IS MADE REGARDING THE RESULTS OF&#xA;THE SOFTWARE OR RELATED SERVICES OR THAT ALL ERRORS IN THE SOFTWARE WILL BE&#xA;CORRECTED, OR THAT THE SOFTWARE&apos;S FUNCTIONALITY WILL MEET LICENSEE&apos;S REQUIREMENTS.&#xA;LICENSEE ACKNOWLEDGES LICENSEE&apos;S RESPONSIBILITY TO (i) REGULARLY BACK UP DATA&#xA;MAINTAINED ON ANY COMPUTER SYSTEM USING THE SOFTWARE AND (ii) ADEQUATELY TEST&#xA;PRIOR TO DEPLOYMENT EACH PRODUCTION VERSION OF THE SOFTWARE IN A CONFIGURATION&#xA;WHICH REASONABLY SIMULATES LICENSEE&apos;S PLANNED DEPLOYMENT OR PRODUCTION&#xA;ENVIRONMENT. This limited warranty gives Licensee specific legal rights. Licensee may have other rights that&#xA;vary among jurisdictions. Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of implied conditions or warranties,&#xA;statutory or otherwise, so the above exclusions may not apply to Licensee.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;10. LIMITATIONS ON LIABILITY. PRAMATI&apos;S LICENSORS SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR DIRECT DAMAGES&#xA;OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER UNDER THIS AGREEMENT. UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL&#xA;PRAMATI, ITS SUBSIDIARIES OR ANY OF ITS LICENSORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOSS OR&#xA;INACCURACY OF DATA, LOSS OF PROFITS OR INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL&#xA;OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES, EVEN IF SUCH PARTY HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF&#xA;SUCH DAMAGES. TOTAL LIABILITY, IF ANY, ARISING OUT OF THIS AGREEMENT OR LICENSEE&apos;S USE&#xA;OF THE SOFTWARE OR RELATED SERVICES SHALL EXCEED THE FEES PAID BY LICENSEE FOR THE&#xA;AFFECTED SOFTWARE OR RELATED SERVICE(S) GIVING RISE TO THE CLAIM. THE FOREGOING&#xA;RESTRICTIONS, DISCLAIMERS AND LIMITATIONS SHALL REMAIN IN FORCE EVEN IN THE EVENT OF A&#xA;FUNDAMENTAL BREACH BY PRAMATI OR A BREACH BY PRAMATI OF A CONDITION OR&#xA;FUNDAMENTAL TERM HEREUNDER. Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion or limitation of indirect,&#xA;special, incidental, consequential or exemplary damages or the limitation of liability to specified amounts, so&#xA;the above limitations or exclusions may not apply to Licensee. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;10.1 Licensee acknowledges that Pramati has no knowledge of, or control over, the installation or use of the&#xA;Software by Licensee. Licensee agrees to defend, indemnify and hold Pramati harmless with respect to any&#xA;suit, claim or proceeding brought against Pramati alleging that installation or use by, or under authority of,&#xA;Licensee of the Software caused personal injury, property damage, or economic loss.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;11. GOVERNING LAW; COMPLETE AGREEMENT. This Agreement shall be construed and enforced in&#xA;accordance with the laws of the State of California, United States of America. The parties agree that venue for&#xA;any dispute under this Agreement shall be San Mateo County, California, U.S.A.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;12. AUDIT RIGHTS.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;12.1 Licensee shall keep accurate records of all activity with respect to use of the Software by Licensee,&#xA;including, without limitation, all Editions of Software used and the number of Named Users accessing the&#xA;Software or the number of CPUs. Licensee shall provide Pramati with summaries of such records upon&#xA;request. At any time during the term of this Agreement, Pramati shall have the right to audit Licensee&apos;s records&#xA;in order to verify that Licensee is limiting use of the Software in accordance with this Agreement. If any audit&#xA;reveals that Licensee is not limiting use of the Software in accordance with this Agreement, Licensee shall&#xA;pay Pramati any underpaid license fees at Pramati&apos;s then current rates within five days of notification of such&#xA;underpayment. If any audit reveals that Licensee has underpaid Pramati by an amount equal to or greater than&#xA;five percent of applicable license fees, Licensee shall also reimburse Pramati for the costs associated with the&#xA;audit.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;13. NOTICES. All notices or other communications required to be given under this Agreement shall be in&#xA;writing and delivered either personally or by mail via an internationally recognized governmental or private mail&#xA;service, certified, return receipt requested, postage prepaid, and addressed as provided in this Agreement or&#xA;as otherwise requested by the receiving party. Notices delivered personally shall be effective upon delivery and&#xA;notices delivered by mail shall be effective upon their receipt by the party to whom they are addressed.&#xA;Licensee shall address all correspondence regarding this Agreement to the Company Secretary of Pramati&#xA;Technologies (P) Ltd. at the Hyderabad, India Office whose address is available at www.pramati.com.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;14. ENTIRE AGREEMENT; MODIFICATIONS AND WAIVERS. This Agreement constitutes the full and entire&#xA;understanding and agreement between the parties with regard to the subjects hereof.  No term of this&#xA;Agreement may be modified except by a writing signed by an authorized representative of each of the parties.&#xA;A waiver by a party of its rights under this Agreement shall not be binding unless contained in a writing signed&#xA;by an authorized representative of the party waiving its rights. The non-enforcement or waiver of any provision&#xA;on one (1) occasion shall not constitute a waiver of such provision on any other occasions unless expressly so&#xA;agreed in writing. It is agreed that no use of trade or other regular practice or method of dealing between the&#xA;parties hereto shall be used to modify, interpret, supplement, or alter in any manner the terms of this&#xA;Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;15. SEVERABILITY. In the event that any provision of this Agreement is found invalid or unenforceable pursuant&#xA;to judicial decree or decision, the remainder of this Agreement shall remain valid and enforceable according to&#xA;its terms.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;16. FORCE MAJEURE. No party shall be responsible for any failure to perform due to unforeseen&#xA;circumstances or to causes beyond the party&apos;s reasonable control, including but not limited to acts of God,&#xA;war, riot, embargoes, acts of civil or military authorities, fire, floods, accidents, strikes, or shortages of&#xA;transportation, facilities, fuel, energy, labor, or materials. In the event of any such delay, a party may defer any&#xA;delivery dates for a period equal to the time of such delay. Notwithstanding the foregoing, if a party is in default&#xA;under this Section for more than fifteen (15) days, the non-defaulting party may terminate this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;17. ARBITRATION. Any controversy or claim arising out of or relating to this Agreement, or the breach thereof&#xA;shall be settled by binding arbitration in the County of San Mateo, California, administered by the American&#xA;Arbitration Association in accordance with its then current Commercial Arbitration Rules, and judgment on the&#xA;award rendered by the arbitrator may be entered in any court having jurisdiction thereof. The arbitrator may&#xA;award monetary damages, punitive damages, injunctive relief, rescission, restitution, costs and attorneys&apos;&#xA;fees. The arbitration award shall be final and binding regardless of whether one of the parties fails or refuses to&#xA;participate in the arbitration. The arbitrator shall not have the power to amend this Agreement in any respect.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;18. ATTORNEYS&apos; FEES. In the event of any dispute with respect to this Agreement, the prevailing party shall&#xA;be entitled to reasonable attorneys&apos; fees and other costs and expenses incurred in resolving such dispute.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;19. TAXES. Unless otherwise agreed between Consultant and Company, Consultant and Company shall each&#xA;have sole responsibility for collecting, reporting, and/or paying all income, sales, excise, property, value-added&#xA;tax, and other taxes imposed by any governmental authority as they pertain to Consultant&apos;s and Company&apos;s&#xA;respective duties, obligations, and performance hereunder.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20. DEFINITIONS.&#xA;&#xA;As used herein, the terms set forth below shall have the following respective meanings:&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.1 &quot;Documentation&quot; means the publications prepared and delivered to Licensee by Pramati that accompanies&#xA;the Software, such as reference, user, installation, systems administrator and technical guides. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.2 &quot;CPU&quot; means each central processing unit designated for use on a specific computing device.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.3 &quot;Software&quot; shall mean the machine readable object code, delivered by Pramati, to Licensee and may&#xA;include software licensed from third parties, together with other software and/or other products subsequently&#xA;delivered to Licensee by Pramati and all updates and upgrades of the same provided to Licensee by Pramati&#xA;and/or its suppliers. Software includes &quot;Server Software&quot; including current release(s) of Pramati Server and&#xA;Pramati Message Server and &quot;Studio Software&quot; including current release(s) of Pramati Studio and &quot;Plugin&#xA;Software&quot;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.4 &quot;Pramati&quot; shall mean Pramati Technologies (P) Limited, as incorporated in the State of Andhra Pradesh,&#xA;India, under Companies Act, 1956, whose address can be found at Pramati&apos;s website at www.pramati.com.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.5 &quot;Licensee&quot; shall mean the entity or individual, either on the individual&apos; s behalf or on behalf of the entity that&#xA;individual represents, who installs the Software or otherwise agrees to be bound by the terms and conditions&#xA;contained in this Agreement. Further, each individual representing an entity represents and warrants that&#xA;he/she has the authority to bind the entity to this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.6 &quot;Named Users&quot; shall mean an individual or individuals employed by Licensee who is/are authorized to use&#xA;the software. The number of licenses for the Program must equal the total number of Named Users.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.7 &quot;Application&quot; shall mean machine-readable object code provided by &quot;Application Provider&quot; to Licensee&#xA;which may be deployed on Software.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.8 &quot;Edition&quot; shall mean either the Standard Edition or the Enterprise Edition of the Software.  The Standard&#xA;Edition does not allow use of certain features available in the Enterprise Edition.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;BY CLICKING THE &quot;ACCEPT&quot; BUTTON OR CHECKING THE &quot;ACCEPT&quot; CHECK-BOX DURING&#xA;INSTALLATION OF THE SOFTWARE, LICENSEE IS AGREEING TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND&#xA;CONDITIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT.&#xA;'/>
        <property name='df_LT.copyright' value='Copyright © 2008 Pramati Technologies. All Rights Reserved.'/>
        <property name='df_LT.featureName' value='Pramati Server 6.0 Plugin'/>
        <property name='df_LT.description' value='Supported server versions 4.1, 5.0 and 6.0'/>
        <property name='df_LT.providerName' value='Pramati Technologies'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.jar' version='2.1.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='feature' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.update.feature' name='com.pramati.eclipse.feature' version='2.1.0'/>
      </provides>
      <filter>
        (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
      </filter>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='org.eclipse.update.feature' id='com.pramati.eclipse.feature' version='2.1.0'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='%25licenseURL' url='%25licenseURL'>
          %license
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        %copyright
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.jar' version='2.2.0'>
      <properties size='8'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%featureName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='%description'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%providerName'/>
        <property name='df_LT.license' value='PRAMATI SOFTWARE END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;THIS IS A LICENSE AND NOT A SALE&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;This License Agreement (&quot;Agreement&quot;) is a legal agreement between Pramati Technologies (P) Ltd. (&quot;Pramati&quot;)&#xA;and the end user licensing the Software and Documentation under this Agreement (&quot;Licensee&quot;). By installing&#xA;the Pramati Server, Pramati Message Server (&quot;Server Software&quot;) and/or Pramati Studio (&quot;Studio Software&quot;) &#xA;and/or Pramati Server Plug-in (&quot;Plugin Software&quot;) (collectively &quot;Software&quot;) Licensee agrees to be bound by the &#xA;terms and conditions set forth in this Agreement. In the event Licensee does not wish to be bound to the terms &#xA;of this Agreement, Licensee must promptly return the Software and Documentation to Pramati together with&#xA;proof of purchase in the manner set forth in Pramati&apos;s return policy found on www.pramati.com in order to &#xA;receive a full refund. All returns must comply.  This Agreement applies to any subsequent purchases of the &#xA;Software or Documentation. Licensee must notify all Named Users of the Software of the terms and conditions &#xA;of this Agreement. The Software is licensed to Licensee, not sold.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;LICENSEE MAY USE THE ENCLOSED SOFTWARE AND DOCUMENTATION ONLY IN ACCORDANCE &#xA;WITH THIS AGREEMENT (UNLESS LICENSEE HAS ALREADY SIGNED A VALID LICENSE AGREEMENT&#xA;WITH PRAMATI OR ONE OF ITS SUBSIDIARIES TO USE THE SOFTWARE).&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.&#x9;LICENSE TERMS. Pramati grants to Licensee, and Licensee accepts from Pramati, a limited non-exclusive&#xA;license to install and use the Software and Documentation in accordance with the applicable License Type set&#xA;forth in Section 1.3, below. All rights not specifically granted to Licensee in this Agreement are retained by&#xA;Pramati and its licensors. Licensee shall not allow the use of the Software except on equipment owned or&#xA;leased by Licensee for Licensee&apos;s business purposes and only by the number of authorized users, as&#xA;applicable for the License Type. Licensee shall not allow the unauthorized use of the Software and&#xA;Documentation and will notify Pramati and pay any additional fees pursuant to Pramati&apos;s then current price list&#xA;before making expanded use of the Software.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.1&#x9;License Key. Pramati provides you with a license key which will give you access to the Software in&#xA;accordance with the applicable License Type Licensee has ordered (&quot;License Key&quot;). Licensee will only receive&#xA;a License Key for an Evaluation License, should Licensee wish to purchase a license after the evaluation&#xA;period Pramati will then provide Licensee with the appropriate License Certificate. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.2&#x9;In addition, Pramati will provide Licensee with a certificate of use, except in the case of an Evaluation&#xA;License or a Development License, which sets forth with specificity the licenses granted to you under this&#xA;Agreement (&quot;License Certificate&quot;). The License Certificate is either sent with this Agreement, or separately by&#xA;electronic mail, or when Licensee downloads the Evaluation License or Developer License and is incorporated&#xA;by reference into this Agreement. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3&#x9;&quot;License Type&quot; for Software shall mean any one of the purposes set forth below for which the Software&#xA;(whether Server Software or Studio Software or Plugin Software, as applicable) has been licensed under this&#xA;Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.1&#x9;&quot;Evaluation License&quot; grants Licensee a thirty (30) day, restricted non-exclusive license to install and use&#xA;the Software subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement. Licensee agrees to use the Software&#xA;under such license solely for evaluation purposes. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.2&#x9;&quot;Deployment License&quot; grants Licensee a non-exclusive license to install and use the Software, limited&#xA;only by the Edition and number of CPUs set forth in the License Certificate for deployment with an unlimited&#xA;number of Licensee&apos;s applications subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.3&#x9;&quot;Production License&quot; grants Licensee a non-exclusive license to install and use the Studio Software,&#xA;limited only by number of Named Users set forth in the License Certificate subject to the terms and provisions&#xA;of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.4&#x9;&quot;Development License&quot; grants Licensee a one hundred eighty (180) day, restricted non-exclusive license&#xA;for the number of developers in Licensee&apos;s organization set forth in the License Certificate to install and use&#xA;the Software solely for Licensee&apos;s internal software application development purposes only and not for any&#xA;other purpose subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement. Licensee may use the media on which&#xA;the Software resides to copy the Software onto those computing devices used by Named Users. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.5&#x9;&quot;Limited License&quot; grants Licensee a restricted non-exclusive license to install and use the Software,&#xA;limited by the Edition and number of CPUs set forth in the License Certificate. Licensee may install and use&#xA;Software for deployment of only a specific named Application developed by Application Provider as set forth in&#xA;the License Certificate subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.6&#x9;&quot;Education License&quot; grants Licensee a one hundred eighty (180) day restricted non-exclusive license to&#xA;install and use the Software, limited by the Edition and restricted by the number of Named Users as set forth in&#xA;the License Certificate solely for the purposes of education, training or academic research subject to the terms&#xA;and provisions of this Agreement. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;2. FEES AND PAYMENT. This is a fee bearing license, Pramati&apos;s current license fees are listed at&#xA;www.pramati.com, All fees resulting from this Agreement are due and payable on Licensee&apos;s receipt of the&#xA;invoice if related to a product or Support Service(s) (as defined in Section 3 below) acquired directly from&#xA;Pramati; otherwise such fees are due and payable in accordance with the applicable authorized reseller&apos;s&#xA;policies. Licensee shall pay all applicable shipping charges, and sales, use, value-added, personal property,&#xA;consumption or similar taxes, tariffs or governmental charges, exclusive of Pramati&apos;s or its reseller&apos;s net&#xA;income and corporate franchise taxes.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;3. SUPPORT SERVICES. Licensee may purchase technical telephone support, update assurance and/or&#xA;training services in support of the Software (&quot;Support Service(s)&quot;) pursuant to a separate support agreement&#xA;and in accordance with then-current plans for such Support Service(s), current versions of which can be found&#xA;within Pramati&apos;s website at &quot;www.pramati.com&quot;. Upgrades will be distributed to Licensee in accordance with&#xA;Pramati&apos;s then current maintenance and support fees, terms and conditions.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;4. RESTRICTIONS AND OTHER CONDITIONS.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(a)&#x9;Except as set forth in Section 4(e) below, Licensee may not copy the Software or Documentation.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(b)&#x9;Licensee may not modify, enhance, reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble, supplement, create&#xA;derivative work from, adapt, translate or otherwise reduce the Software to human readable form (except as&#xA;specifically permitted in the Documentation). Notwithstanding the foregoing, in the event Licensee is located in&#xA;the European Economic Area and there is a legal requirement in this area to have access to the source code&#xA;of the Software to achieve interoperability of the Software with other software, Licensee shall notify Pramati&#xA;and Pramati can at its sole option choose to either (i) perform the work in order to achieve such interoperability&#xA;at its then-standard rates for such work to Licensee or (ii) to permit Licensee to reverse engineer parts of the&#xA;Software in order to obtain such source code, but only to the extent necessary to achieve such interoperability.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(c)&#x9;Licensee may not rent or lease the Software to third parties, nor allow use of the Software for service&#xA;bureau, timesharing, application service provider or any other form of shared use.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(d)&#x9;Except as otherwise expressly permitted in this Agreement, Licensee may not cause or permit the&#xA;disclosure, copying, renting, licensing, sublicensing, leasing, dissemination or other distribution of the&#xA;Software or its Documentation by any means or in any form to any third party including, without limitation, any&#xA;form of distributor or reseller without a signed agreement with Pramati granting such right(s).&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(e)&#x9;Licensee may make one copy of the Software and Documentation solely for archival, emergency back-up,&#xA;or disaster recovery purposes; provided, however, that all copyright and other proprietary notices of Pramati and&#xA;its licensors are reproduced on such copies.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(f)&#x9;Licensee acknowledges that, although the Software media may contain other software products, Licensee is&#xA;hereby licensed to install and use only the Software designated by the License Key and the License&#xA;Certificate provided to Licensee for operation of the Software.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(g)&#x9;The Software may not be transferred, sold, assigned or otherwise conveyed (whether by operation of law&#xA;or otherwise) to another party or outside the country in which it was originally delivered to Licensee without&#xA;Pramati&apos;s prior written consent subject to Licensee&apos;s compliance with all applicable export and re-export&#xA;regulations and restrictions; provided, however, that if Licensee is located in the European Economic Area, and&#xA;is a legal requirement in this area, Licensee may transfer Licensee&apos;s copy of the Software together with its&#xA;Documentation on a permanent basis, so long as Licensee notifies Pramati as to the name and address of the&#xA;recipient of Licensee&apos;s copy and that such recipient agrees in writing to be bound by the terms and conditions&#xA;of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(h)&#x9;Results of benchmark or other performance tests run on the Software may not be disclosed to any third&#xA;party without Pramati&apos;s prior written consent.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(i)&#x9;The Software contains software programs written in Java. The Software is not fault-tolerant and is not&#xA;designed, manufactured or intended for use or resale in the on-line control, design, construction, operation or&#xA;maintenance of any nuclear facilities, aircraft navigation or communication systems, air traffic control, direct&#xA;life support machines, or weapons systems, in which the failure of the Software could lead directly to death,&#xA;personal injury, or severe physical or environmental damage (&quot;High Risk Activities&quot;). Pramati and its suppliers&#xA;specifically disclaim any express or implied warranty of fitness for High Risk Activities. Licensee agrees that it&#xA;is not licensed to use the Software for High Risk Activities and that failure to comply with this section will result&#xA;in immediate termination of this Agreement without refund.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(j)&#x9;Third party software products supplied with the Software are provided to Licensee subject to such third&#xA;party&apos;s license agreement with Pramati, the terms of which may change from time to time. The Cloudscape&#xA;software products may only be used as a part of Pramati&apos;s development Software. The Cloudscape software&#xA;products may only be used on the operating system platforms on which Informix has made the Cloudscape&#xA;software generally commercially available. Licensee may not copy, distribute, or otherwise deploy the&#xA;Cloudscape software products or any other programs developed using such Cloudscape software. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;GENERAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;5. COPYRIGHT AND OWNERSHIP. Title, ownership rights, and all intellectual property rights in and to the&#xA;Software and Documentation including all copies thereof, and all rights therein including, but not limited to, all&#xA;trade secrets, trademarks, patents, copyrights, trade secrets and moral rights shall remain the sole and&#xA;exclusive property of Pramati and/or its licensors. Licensee acknowledges that the Software contains valuable&#xA;confidential information and trade secrets of Pramati and/or its licensors. No title or ownership to the Software&#xA;or Documentation or any part or modification thereof is transferred to Licensee. Software is protected by&#xA;copyright laws and international treaty provisions. Licensee shall not remove or alter Pramati&apos;s or any third&#xA;party&apos; s ownership, trademark, copyright, or other proprietary notices on the Software or Documentation.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;5.1 Pramati acknowledges that Software contains third-party software as listed in the attached files.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;5.2 Licensee acknowledges that Software contains software from third-party and agrees to abide by the&#xA;third-party agreements attached hereto. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;6. U.S. GOVERNMENT RIGHTS. If the Software or its Documentation is acquired by or on behalf of the United&#xA;States Government, the United States Government agrees that such Software and Documentation is&#xA;&quot;commercial computer software&quot; or &quot;commercial computer software documentation&quot; and that use,&#xA;modification, duplication and disclosure of the Software and its Documentation by the United States&#xA;Government is subject to restrictions set forth in this Agreement or in a written agreement to the contrary&#xA;specifying the United States Government&apos;s right to use the Software and its Documentation, pursuant to FAR&#xA;§ 12.212(a) and/or DFARS § 227.7202-1(a), as applicable. Pramati reserves all unpublished rights under U.S.&#xA;copyright laws.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;7. TERM OF LICENSE. Either party may terminate this Agreement if the other party materially breaches any of&#xA;its obligations hereunder and fails to cure such breach within thirty (30) days after written notice. Upon&#xA;termination, all rights granted to Licensee hereunder shall terminate and Licensee shall cease using the&#xA;Software, and within five (5) days of termination Licensee shall destroy or return to Pramati all copies of the&#xA;Software and its Documentation in any form. Upon request, Licensee shall certify that all copies of the&#xA;Software have been destroyed. Termination of this Agreement will not affect any provisions relating to the&#xA;payment of amounts due, limiting or disclaiming Pramati&apos;s liability, confidentiality, and ownership of copyrights&#xA;and other intellectual property of Pramati including, but not limited to, the Software and Documentation, which&#xA;provisions will survive termination of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;8. CONFIDENTIALITY.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;8.1 Definition. Licensee agrees that information disclosed to it by Pramati including, but not limited to,&#xA;information learned or developed using the Software or Documentation, or that relates to its products, designs,&#xA;research, development, know-how, or third party confidential information, will be considered and referred to &#xA;collectively in this Agreement as &quot;Confidential Information.&quot; Confidential Information, however, does not include&#xA;information that 1) is now or subsequently becomes generally available to the public through no fault or breach&#xA;on the part of Licensee; 2) Licensee can demonstrate to have had rightfully in its possession prior to&#xA;disclosure by Pramati of such Confidential Information; 3) is independently developed by Licensee without the&#xA;use of any Confidential Information, the Software or Documentation of Pramati; or 4) Licensee rightfully obtains&#xA;from a third party who has the right to transfer or disclose it.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;8.2 Nondisclosure and Nonuse of Confidential Information. Except as otherwise set forth in this Agreement,&#xA;Licensee agrees that it will not disclosure, publish, or disseminate Confidential Information of Pramati to&#xA;anyone other than those of its employees with a demonstrated need to know, and Licensee agrees to take all&#xA;reasonable precautions to prevent any unauthorized use, disclosure, publication, or dissemination of&#xA;Confidential Information. Licensee agrees to use any Confidential Information disclosed to it solely for the&#xA;purposes contemplated by this Agreement and not otherwise for its own or any third party&apos;s benefit without the&#xA;prior written approval of an authorized representative of Pramati in each instance. All Confidential Information&#xA;remains the property of Pramati. Licensee shall enter into appropriate agreements, if Licensee has not already&#xA;done so, to protect the Confidential Information. Licensee shall not use Confidential Information at any time for&#xA;any purpose other than as authorized by Pramati.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;9. LIMITED WARRANTY. For a period of thirty (30) days from the date of Licensee&apos;s receipt of the Software,&#xA;Pramati warrants that the Software, when properly installed and used with the equipment configuration and in&#xA;the operating environment specified by Pramati, will operate in all material respects in conformity with its&#xA;Documentation, and the Software media shall be free of defects. Pramati warrants that Software telephone&#xA;support and training services (&quot;Related Service(s)&quot;) will be performed by qualified personnel in a professional&#xA;manner. In the event of non-conforming Software or Related Service(s), or if the media is defective, Licensee&apos;s&#xA;sole remedy and Pramati&apos;s exclusive liability shall be, as applicable and at Pramati&apos;s option, replacement of&#xA;the affected Software or media, or re-performance of the Related Service(s) at no additional charge, or a refund&#xA;of the fees paid for the affected Software or Related Service(s). EVALUATION SOFTWARE AND ANY THIRD&#xA;PARTY SOFTWARE ARE PROVIDED TO LICENSEE &quot;AS IS&quot; WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY, EXPRESS OR&#xA;IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE. PRAMATI DISCLAIMS ALL OTHER WARRANTIES AND&#xA;CONDITIONS, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION&#xA;THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND&#xA;WHETHER ARISING BY STATUTE OR IN LAW OR AS A RESULT OF A COURSE OF DEALING OR&#xA;USAGE OF TRADE, WITH RESPECT TO THE SOFTWARE, ITS DOCUMENTATION, SUPPORT OR OTHER&#xA;SERVICES RELATED TO THE SOFTWARE. NO WARRANTY IS MADE REGARDING THE RESULTS OF&#xA;THE SOFTWARE OR RELATED SERVICES OR THAT ALL ERRORS IN THE SOFTWARE WILL BE&#xA;CORRECTED, OR THAT THE SOFTWARE&apos;S FUNCTIONALITY WILL MEET LICENSEE&apos;S REQUIREMENTS.&#xA;LICENSEE ACKNOWLEDGES LICENSEE&apos;S RESPONSIBILITY TO (i) REGULARLY BACK UP DATA&#xA;MAINTAINED ON ANY COMPUTER SYSTEM USING THE SOFTWARE AND (ii) ADEQUATELY TEST&#xA;PRIOR TO DEPLOYMENT EACH PRODUCTION VERSION OF THE SOFTWARE IN A CONFIGURATION&#xA;WHICH REASONABLY SIMULATES LICENSEE&apos;S PLANNED DEPLOYMENT OR PRODUCTION&#xA;ENVIRONMENT. This limited warranty gives Licensee specific legal rights. Licensee may have other rights that&#xA;vary among jurisdictions. Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of implied conditions or warranties,&#xA;statutory or otherwise, so the above exclusions may not apply to Licensee.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;10. LIMITATIONS ON LIABILITY. PRAMATI&apos;S LICENSORS SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR DIRECT DAMAGES&#xA;OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER UNDER THIS AGREEMENT. UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL&#xA;PRAMATI, ITS SUBSIDIARIES OR ANY OF ITS LICENSORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOSS OR&#xA;INACCURACY OF DATA, LOSS OF PROFITS OR INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL&#xA;OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES, EVEN IF SUCH PARTY HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF&#xA;SUCH DAMAGES. TOTAL LIABILITY, IF ANY, ARISING OUT OF THIS AGREEMENT OR LICENSEE&apos;S USE&#xA;OF THE SOFTWARE OR RELATED SERVICES SHALL EXCEED THE FEES PAID BY LICENSEE FOR THE&#xA;AFFECTED SOFTWARE OR RELATED SERVICE(S) GIVING RISE TO THE CLAIM. THE FOREGOING&#xA;RESTRICTIONS, DISCLAIMERS AND LIMITATIONS SHALL REMAIN IN FORCE EVEN IN THE EVENT OF A&#xA;FUNDAMENTAL BREACH BY PRAMATI OR A BREACH BY PRAMATI OF A CONDITION OR&#xA;FUNDAMENTAL TERM HEREUNDER. Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion or limitation of indirect,&#xA;special, incidental, consequential or exemplary damages or the limitation of liability to specified amounts, so&#xA;the above limitations or exclusions may not apply to Licensee. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;10.1 Licensee acknowledges that Pramati has no knowledge of, or control over, the installation or use of the&#xA;Software by Licensee. Licensee agrees to defend, indemnify and hold Pramati harmless with respect to any&#xA;suit, claim or proceeding brought against Pramati alleging that installation or use by, or under authority of,&#xA;Licensee of the Software caused personal injury, property damage, or economic loss.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;11. GOVERNING LAW; COMPLETE AGREEMENT. This Agreement shall be construed and enforced in&#xA;accordance with the laws of the State of California, United States of America. The parties agree that venue for&#xA;any dispute under this Agreement shall be San Mateo County, California, U.S.A.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;12. AUDIT RIGHTS.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;12.1 Licensee shall keep accurate records of all activity with respect to use of the Software by Licensee,&#xA;including, without limitation, all Editions of Software used and the number of Named Users accessing the&#xA;Software or the number of CPUs. Licensee shall provide Pramati with summaries of such records upon&#xA;request. At any time during the term of this Agreement, Pramati shall have the right to audit Licensee&apos;s records&#xA;in order to verify that Licensee is limiting use of the Software in accordance with this Agreement. If any audit&#xA;reveals that Licensee is not limiting use of the Software in accordance with this Agreement, Licensee shall&#xA;pay Pramati any underpaid license fees at Pramati&apos;s then current rates within five days of notification of such&#xA;underpayment. If any audit reveals that Licensee has underpaid Pramati by an amount equal to or greater than&#xA;five percent of applicable license fees, Licensee shall also reimburse Pramati for the costs associated with the&#xA;audit.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;13. NOTICES. All notices or other communications required to be given under this Agreement shall be in&#xA;writing and delivered either personally or by mail via an internationally recognized governmental or private mail&#xA;service, certified, return receipt requested, postage prepaid, and addressed as provided in this Agreement or&#xA;as otherwise requested by the receiving party. Notices delivered personally shall be effective upon delivery and&#xA;notices delivered by mail shall be effective upon their receipt by the party to whom they are addressed.&#xA;Licensee shall address all correspondence regarding this Agreement to the Company Secretary of Pramati&#xA;Technologies (P) Ltd. at the Hyderabad, India Office whose address is available at www.pramati.com.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;14. ENTIRE AGREEMENT; MODIFICATIONS AND WAIVERS. This Agreement constitutes the full and entire&#xA;understanding and agreement between the parties with regard to the subjects hereof.  No term of this&#xA;Agreement may be modified except by a writing signed by an authorized representative of each of the parties.&#xA;A waiver by a party of its rights under this Agreement shall not be binding unless contained in a writing signed&#xA;by an authorized representative of the party waiving its rights. The non-enforcement or waiver of any provision&#xA;on one (1) occasion shall not constitute a waiver of such provision on any other occasions unless expressly so&#xA;agreed in writing. It is agreed that no use of trade or other regular practice or method of dealing between the&#xA;parties hereto shall be used to modify, interpret, supplement, or alter in any manner the terms of this&#xA;Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;15. SEVERABILITY. In the event that any provision of this Agreement is found invalid or unenforceable pursuant&#xA;to judicial decree or decision, the remainder of this Agreement shall remain valid and enforceable according to&#xA;its terms.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;16. FORCE MAJEURE. No party shall be responsible for any failure to perform due to unforeseen&#xA;circumstances or to causes beyond the party&apos;s reasonable control, including but not limited to acts of God,&#xA;war, riot, embargoes, acts of civil or military authorities, fire, floods, accidents, strikes, or shortages of&#xA;transportation, facilities, fuel, energy, labor, or materials. In the event of any such delay, a party may defer any&#xA;delivery dates for a period equal to the time of such delay. Notwithstanding the foregoing, if a party is in default&#xA;under this Section for more than fifteen (15) days, the non-defaulting party may terminate this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;17. ARBITRATION. Any controversy or claim arising out of or relating to this Agreement, or the breach thereof&#xA;shall be settled by binding arbitration in the County of San Mateo, California, administered by the American&#xA;Arbitration Association in accordance with its then current Commercial Arbitration Rules, and judgment on the&#xA;award rendered by the arbitrator may be entered in any court having jurisdiction thereof. The arbitrator may&#xA;award monetary damages, punitive damages, injunctive relief, rescission, restitution, costs and attorneys&apos;&#xA;fees. The arbitration award shall be final and binding regardless of whether one of the parties fails or refuses to&#xA;participate in the arbitration. The arbitrator shall not have the power to amend this Agreement in any respect.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;18. ATTORNEYS&apos; FEES. In the event of any dispute with respect to this Agreement, the prevailing party shall&#xA;be entitled to reasonable attorneys&apos; fees and other costs and expenses incurred in resolving such dispute.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;19. TAXES. Unless otherwise agreed between Consultant and Company, Consultant and Company shall each&#xA;have sole responsibility for collecting, reporting, and/or paying all income, sales, excise, property, value-added&#xA;tax, and other taxes imposed by any governmental authority as they pertain to Consultant&apos;s and Company&apos;s&#xA;respective duties, obligations, and performance hereunder.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20. DEFINITIONS.&#xA;&#xA;As used herein, the terms set forth below shall have the following respective meanings:&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.1 &quot;Documentation&quot; means the publications prepared and delivered to Licensee by Pramati that accompanies&#xA;the Software, such as reference, user, installation, systems administrator and technical guides. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.2 &quot;CPU&quot; means each central processing unit designated for use on a specific computing device.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.3 &quot;Software&quot; shall mean the machine readable object code, delivered by Pramati, to Licensee and may&#xA;include software licensed from third parties, together with other software and/or other products subsequently&#xA;delivered to Licensee by Pramati and all updates and upgrades of the same provided to Licensee by Pramati&#xA;and/or its suppliers. Software includes &quot;Server Software&quot; including current release(s) of Pramati Server and&#xA;Pramati Message Server and &quot;Studio Software&quot; including current release(s) of Pramati Studio and &quot;Plugin&#xA;Software&quot;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.4 &quot;Pramati&quot; shall mean Pramati Technologies (P) Limited, as incorporated in the State of Andhra Pradesh,&#xA;India, under Companies Act, 1956, whose address can be found at Pramati&apos;s website at www.pramati.com.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.5 &quot;Licensee&quot; shall mean the entity or individual, either on the individual&apos; s behalf or on behalf of the entity that&#xA;individual represents, who installs the Software or otherwise agrees to be bound by the terms and conditions&#xA;contained in this Agreement. Further, each individual representing an entity represents and warrants that&#xA;he/she has the authority to bind the entity to this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.6 &quot;Named Users&quot; shall mean an individual or individuals employed by Licensee who is/are authorized to use&#xA;the software. The number of licenses for the Program must equal the total number of Named Users.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.7 &quot;Application&quot; shall mean machine-readable object code provided by &quot;Application Provider&quot; to Licensee&#xA;which may be deployed on Software.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.8 &quot;Edition&quot; shall mean either the Standard Edition or the Enterprise Edition of the Software.  The Standard&#xA;Edition does not allow use of certain features available in the Enterprise Edition.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;BY CLICKING THE &quot;ACCEPT&quot; BUTTON OR CHECKING THE &quot;ACCEPT&quot; CHECK-BOX DURING&#xA;INSTALLATION OF THE SOFTWARE, LICENSEE IS AGREEING TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND&#xA;CONDITIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT.&#xA;'/>
        <property name='df_LT.copyright' value='Copyright © 2008 Pramati Technologies. All Rights Reserved.'/>
        <property name='df_LT.featureName' value='Pramati Server 6.5 Plugin'/>
        <property name='df_LT.description' value='Supported server versions 4.1, 5.0, 6.0 and 6.5'/>
        <property name='df_LT.providerName' value='Pramati Technologies'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.jar' version='2.2.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='feature' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.update.feature' name='com.pramati.eclipse.feature' version='2.2.0'/>
      </provides>
      <filter>
        (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
      </filter>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='org.eclipse.update.feature' id='com.pramati.eclipse.feature' version='2.2.0'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='%25licenseURL' url='%25licenseURL'>
          %license
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        %copyright
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.group' version='2.1.0' singleton='false'>
      <update id='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.group' range='[0.0.0,2.1.0)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='9'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%featureName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='%description'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%providerName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.group' value='true'/>
        <property name='df_LT.license' value='PRAMATI SOFTWARE END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;THIS IS A LICENSE AND NOT A SALE&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;This License Agreement (&quot;Agreement&quot;) is a legal agreement between Pramati Technologies (P) Ltd. (&quot;Pramati&quot;)&#xA;and the end user licensing the Software and Documentation under this Agreement (&quot;Licensee&quot;). By installing&#xA;the Pramati Server, Pramati Message Server (&quot;Server Software&quot;) and/or Pramati Studio (&quot;Studio Software&quot;) &#xA;and/or Pramati Server Plug-in (&quot;Plugin Software&quot;) (collectively &quot;Software&quot;) Licensee agrees to be bound by the &#xA;terms and conditions set forth in this Agreement. In the event Licensee does not wish to be bound to the terms &#xA;of this Agreement, Licensee must promptly return the Software and Documentation to Pramati together with&#xA;proof of purchase in the manner set forth in Pramati&apos;s return policy found on www.pramati.com in order to &#xA;receive a full refund. All returns must comply.  This Agreement applies to any subsequent purchases of the &#xA;Software or Documentation. Licensee must notify all Named Users of the Software of the terms and conditions &#xA;of this Agreement. The Software is licensed to Licensee, not sold.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;LICENSEE MAY USE THE ENCLOSED SOFTWARE AND DOCUMENTATION ONLY IN ACCORDANCE &#xA;WITH THIS AGREEMENT (UNLESS LICENSEE HAS ALREADY SIGNED A VALID LICENSE AGREEMENT&#xA;WITH PRAMATI OR ONE OF ITS SUBSIDIARIES TO USE THE SOFTWARE).&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.&#x9;LICENSE TERMS. Pramati grants to Licensee, and Licensee accepts from Pramati, a limited non-exclusive&#xA;license to install and use the Software and Documentation in accordance with the applicable License Type set&#xA;forth in Section 1.3, below. All rights not specifically granted to Licensee in this Agreement are retained by&#xA;Pramati and its licensors. Licensee shall not allow the use of the Software except on equipment owned or&#xA;leased by Licensee for Licensee&apos;s business purposes and only by the number of authorized users, as&#xA;applicable for the License Type. Licensee shall not allow the unauthorized use of the Software and&#xA;Documentation and will notify Pramati and pay any additional fees pursuant to Pramati&apos;s then current price list&#xA;before making expanded use of the Software.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.1&#x9;License Key. Pramati provides you with a license key which will give you access to the Software in&#xA;accordance with the applicable License Type Licensee has ordered (&quot;License Key&quot;). Licensee will only receive&#xA;a License Key for an Evaluation License, should Licensee wish to purchase a license after the evaluation&#xA;period Pramati will then provide Licensee with the appropriate License Certificate. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.2&#x9;In addition, Pramati will provide Licensee with a certificate of use, except in the case of an Evaluation&#xA;License or a Development License, which sets forth with specificity the licenses granted to you under this&#xA;Agreement (&quot;License Certificate&quot;). The License Certificate is either sent with this Agreement, or separately by&#xA;electronic mail, or when Licensee downloads the Evaluation License or Developer License and is incorporated&#xA;by reference into this Agreement. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3&#x9;&quot;License Type&quot; for Software shall mean any one of the purposes set forth below for which the Software&#xA;(whether Server Software or Studio Software or Plugin Software, as applicable) has been licensed under this&#xA;Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.1&#x9;&quot;Evaluation License&quot; grants Licensee a thirty (30) day, restricted non-exclusive license to install and use&#xA;the Software subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement. Licensee agrees to use the Software&#xA;under such license solely for evaluation purposes. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.2&#x9;&quot;Deployment License&quot; grants Licensee a non-exclusive license to install and use the Software, limited&#xA;only by the Edition and number of CPUs set forth in the License Certificate for deployment with an unlimited&#xA;number of Licensee&apos;s applications subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.3&#x9;&quot;Production License&quot; grants Licensee a non-exclusive license to install and use the Studio Software,&#xA;limited only by number of Named Users set forth in the License Certificate subject to the terms and provisions&#xA;of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.4&#x9;&quot;Development License&quot; grants Licensee a one hundred eighty (180) day, restricted non-exclusive license&#xA;for the number of developers in Licensee&apos;s organization set forth in the License Certificate to install and use&#xA;the Software solely for Licensee&apos;s internal software application development purposes only and not for any&#xA;other purpose subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement. Licensee may use the media on which&#xA;the Software resides to copy the Software onto those computing devices used by Named Users. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.5&#x9;&quot;Limited License&quot; grants Licensee a restricted non-exclusive license to install and use the Software,&#xA;limited by the Edition and number of CPUs set forth in the License Certificate. Licensee may install and use&#xA;Software for deployment of only a specific named Application developed by Application Provider as set forth in&#xA;the License Certificate subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.6&#x9;&quot;Education License&quot; grants Licensee a one hundred eighty (180) day restricted non-exclusive license to&#xA;install and use the Software, limited by the Edition and restricted by the number of Named Users as set forth in&#xA;the License Certificate solely for the purposes of education, training or academic research subject to the terms&#xA;and provisions of this Agreement. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;2. FEES AND PAYMENT. This is a fee bearing license, Pramati&apos;s current license fees are listed at&#xA;www.pramati.com, All fees resulting from this Agreement are due and payable on Licensee&apos;s receipt of the&#xA;invoice if related to a product or Support Service(s) (as defined in Section 3 below) acquired directly from&#xA;Pramati; otherwise such fees are due and payable in accordance with the applicable authorized reseller&apos;s&#xA;policies. Licensee shall pay all applicable shipping charges, and sales, use, value-added, personal property,&#xA;consumption or similar taxes, tariffs or governmental charges, exclusive of Pramati&apos;s or its reseller&apos;s net&#xA;income and corporate franchise taxes.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;3. SUPPORT SERVICES. Licensee may purchase technical telephone support, update assurance and/or&#xA;training services in support of the Software (&quot;Support Service(s)&quot;) pursuant to a separate support agreement&#xA;and in accordance with then-current plans for such Support Service(s), current versions of which can be found&#xA;within Pramati&apos;s website at &quot;www.pramati.com&quot;. Upgrades will be distributed to Licensee in accordance with&#xA;Pramati&apos;s then current maintenance and support fees, terms and conditions.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;4. RESTRICTIONS AND OTHER CONDITIONS.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(a)&#x9;Except as set forth in Section 4(e) below, Licensee may not copy the Software or Documentation.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(b)&#x9;Licensee may not modify, enhance, reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble, supplement, create&#xA;derivative work from, adapt, translate or otherwise reduce the Software to human readable form (except as&#xA;specifically permitted in the Documentation). Notwithstanding the foregoing, in the event Licensee is located in&#xA;the European Economic Area and there is a legal requirement in this area to have access to the source code&#xA;of the Software to achieve interoperability of the Software with other software, Licensee shall notify Pramati&#xA;and Pramati can at its sole option choose to either (i) perform the work in order to achieve such interoperability&#xA;at its then-standard rates for such work to Licensee or (ii) to permit Licensee to reverse engineer parts of the&#xA;Software in order to obtain such source code, but only to the extent necessary to achieve such interoperability.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(c)&#x9;Licensee may not rent or lease the Software to third parties, nor allow use of the Software for service&#xA;bureau, timesharing, application service provider or any other form of shared use.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(d)&#x9;Except as otherwise expressly permitted in this Agreement, Licensee may not cause or permit the&#xA;disclosure, copying, renting, licensing, sublicensing, leasing, dissemination or other distribution of the&#xA;Software or its Documentation by any means or in any form to any third party including, without limitation, any&#xA;form of distributor or reseller without a signed agreement with Pramati granting such right(s).&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(e)&#x9;Licensee may make one copy of the Software and Documentation solely for archival, emergency back-up,&#xA;or disaster recovery purposes; provided, however, that all copyright and other proprietary notices of Pramati and&#xA;its licensors are reproduced on such copies.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(f)&#x9;Licensee acknowledges that, although the Software media may contain other software products, Licensee is&#xA;hereby licensed to install and use only the Software designated by the License Key and the License&#xA;Certificate provided to Licensee for operation of the Software.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(g)&#x9;The Software may not be transferred, sold, assigned or otherwise conveyed (whether by operation of law&#xA;or otherwise) to another party or outside the country in which it was originally delivered to Licensee without&#xA;Pramati&apos;s prior written consent subject to Licensee&apos;s compliance with all applicable export and re-export&#xA;regulations and restrictions; provided, however, that if Licensee is located in the European Economic Area, and&#xA;is a legal requirement in this area, Licensee may transfer Licensee&apos;s copy of the Software together with its&#xA;Documentation on a permanent basis, so long as Licensee notifies Pramati as to the name and address of the&#xA;recipient of Licensee&apos;s copy and that such recipient agrees in writing to be bound by the terms and conditions&#xA;of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(h)&#x9;Results of benchmark or other performance tests run on the Software may not be disclosed to any third&#xA;party without Pramati&apos;s prior written consent.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(i)&#x9;The Software contains software programs written in Java. The Software is not fault-tolerant and is not&#xA;designed, manufactured or intended for use or resale in the on-line control, design, construction, operation or&#xA;maintenance of any nuclear facilities, aircraft navigation or communication systems, air traffic control, direct&#xA;life support machines, or weapons systems, in which the failure of the Software could lead directly to death,&#xA;personal injury, or severe physical or environmental damage (&quot;High Risk Activities&quot;). Pramati and its suppliers&#xA;specifically disclaim any express or implied warranty of fitness for High Risk Activities. Licensee agrees that it&#xA;is not licensed to use the Software for High Risk Activities and that failure to comply with this section will result&#xA;in immediate termination of this Agreement without refund.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(j)&#x9;Third party software products supplied with the Software are provided to Licensee subject to such third&#xA;party&apos;s license agreement with Pramati, the terms of which may change from time to time. The Cloudscape&#xA;software products may only be used as a part of Pramati&apos;s development Software. The Cloudscape software&#xA;products may only be used on the operating system platforms on which Informix has made the Cloudscape&#xA;software generally commercially available. Licensee may not copy, distribute, or otherwise deploy the&#xA;Cloudscape software products or any other programs developed using such Cloudscape software. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;GENERAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;5. COPYRIGHT AND OWNERSHIP. Title, ownership rights, and all intellectual property rights in and to the&#xA;Software and Documentation including all copies thereof, and all rights therein including, but not limited to, all&#xA;trade secrets, trademarks, patents, copyrights, trade secrets and moral rights shall remain the sole and&#xA;exclusive property of Pramati and/or its licensors. Licensee acknowledges that the Software contains valuable&#xA;confidential information and trade secrets of Pramati and/or its licensors. No title or ownership to the Software&#xA;or Documentation or any part or modification thereof is transferred to Licensee. Software is protected by&#xA;copyright laws and international treaty provisions. Licensee shall not remove or alter Pramati&apos;s or any third&#xA;party&apos; s ownership, trademark, copyright, or other proprietary notices on the Software or Documentation.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;5.1 Pramati acknowledges that Software contains third-party software as listed in the attached files.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;5.2 Licensee acknowledges that Software contains software from third-party and agrees to abide by the&#xA;third-party agreements attached hereto. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;6. U.S. GOVERNMENT RIGHTS. If the Software or its Documentation is acquired by or on behalf of the United&#xA;States Government, the United States Government agrees that such Software and Documentation is&#xA;&quot;commercial computer software&quot; or &quot;commercial computer software documentation&quot; and that use,&#xA;modification, duplication and disclosure of the Software and its Documentation by the United States&#xA;Government is subject to restrictions set forth in this Agreement or in a written agreement to the contrary&#xA;specifying the United States Government&apos;s right to use the Software and its Documentation, pursuant to FAR&#xA;§ 12.212(a) and/or DFARS § 227.7202-1(a), as applicable. Pramati reserves all unpublished rights under U.S.&#xA;copyright laws.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;7. TERM OF LICENSE. Either party may terminate this Agreement if the other party materially breaches any of&#xA;its obligations hereunder and fails to cure such breach within thirty (30) days after written notice. Upon&#xA;termination, all rights granted to Licensee hereunder shall terminate and Licensee shall cease using the&#xA;Software, and within five (5) days of termination Licensee shall destroy or return to Pramati all copies of the&#xA;Software and its Documentation in any form. Upon request, Licensee shall certify that all copies of the&#xA;Software have been destroyed. Termination of this Agreement will not affect any provisions relating to the&#xA;payment of amounts due, limiting or disclaiming Pramati&apos;s liability, confidentiality, and ownership of copyrights&#xA;and other intellectual property of Pramati including, but not limited to, the Software and Documentation, which&#xA;provisions will survive termination of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;8. CONFIDENTIALITY.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;8.1 Definition. Licensee agrees that information disclosed to it by Pramati including, but not limited to,&#xA;information learned or developed using the Software or Documentation, or that relates to its products, designs,&#xA;research, development, know-how, or third party confidential information, will be considered and referred to &#xA;collectively in this Agreement as &quot;Confidential Information.&quot; Confidential Information, however, does not include&#xA;information that 1) is now or subsequently becomes generally available to the public through no fault or breach&#xA;on the part of Licensee; 2) Licensee can demonstrate to have had rightfully in its possession prior to&#xA;disclosure by Pramati of such Confidential Information; 3) is independently developed by Licensee without the&#xA;use of any Confidential Information, the Software or Documentation of Pramati; or 4) Licensee rightfully obtains&#xA;from a third party who has the right to transfer or disclose it.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;8.2 Nondisclosure and Nonuse of Confidential Information. Except as otherwise set forth in this Agreement,&#xA;Licensee agrees that it will not disclosure, publish, or disseminate Confidential Information of Pramati to&#xA;anyone other than those of its employees with a demonstrated need to know, and Licensee agrees to take all&#xA;reasonable precautions to prevent any unauthorized use, disclosure, publication, or dissemination of&#xA;Confidential Information. Licensee agrees to use any Confidential Information disclosed to it solely for the&#xA;purposes contemplated by this Agreement and not otherwise for its own or any third party&apos;s benefit without the&#xA;prior written approval of an authorized representative of Pramati in each instance. All Confidential Information&#xA;remains the property of Pramati. Licensee shall enter into appropriate agreements, if Licensee has not already&#xA;done so, to protect the Confidential Information. Licensee shall not use Confidential Information at any time for&#xA;any purpose other than as authorized by Pramati.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;9. LIMITED WARRANTY. For a period of thirty (30) days from the date of Licensee&apos;s receipt of the Software,&#xA;Pramati warrants that the Software, when properly installed and used with the equipment configuration and in&#xA;the operating environment specified by Pramati, will operate in all material respects in conformity with its&#xA;Documentation, and the Software media shall be free of defects. Pramati warrants that Software telephone&#xA;support and training services (&quot;Related Service(s)&quot;) will be performed by qualified personnel in a professional&#xA;manner. In the event of non-conforming Software or Related Service(s), or if the media is defective, Licensee&apos;s&#xA;sole remedy and Pramati&apos;s exclusive liability shall be, as applicable and at Pramati&apos;s option, replacement of&#xA;the affected Software or media, or re-performance of the Related Service(s) at no additional charge, or a refund&#xA;of the fees paid for the affected Software or Related Service(s). EVALUATION SOFTWARE AND ANY THIRD&#xA;PARTY SOFTWARE ARE PROVIDED TO LICENSEE &quot;AS IS&quot; WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY, EXPRESS OR&#xA;IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE. PRAMATI DISCLAIMS ALL OTHER WARRANTIES AND&#xA;CONDITIONS, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION&#xA;THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND&#xA;WHETHER ARISING BY STATUTE OR IN LAW OR AS A RESULT OF A COURSE OF DEALING OR&#xA;USAGE OF TRADE, WITH RESPECT TO THE SOFTWARE, ITS DOCUMENTATION, SUPPORT OR OTHER&#xA;SERVICES RELATED TO THE SOFTWARE. NO WARRANTY IS MADE REGARDING THE RESULTS OF&#xA;THE SOFTWARE OR RELATED SERVICES OR THAT ALL ERRORS IN THE SOFTWARE WILL BE&#xA;CORRECTED, OR THAT THE SOFTWARE&apos;S FUNCTIONALITY WILL MEET LICENSEE&apos;S REQUIREMENTS.&#xA;LICENSEE ACKNOWLEDGES LICENSEE&apos;S RESPONSIBILITY TO (i) REGULARLY BACK UP DATA&#xA;MAINTAINED ON ANY COMPUTER SYSTEM USING THE SOFTWARE AND (ii) ADEQUATELY TEST&#xA;PRIOR TO DEPLOYMENT EACH PRODUCTION VERSION OF THE SOFTWARE IN A CONFIGURATION&#xA;WHICH REASONABLY SIMULATES LICENSEE&apos;S PLANNED DEPLOYMENT OR PRODUCTION&#xA;ENVIRONMENT. This limited warranty gives Licensee specific legal rights. Licensee may have other rights that&#xA;vary among jurisdictions. Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of implied conditions or warranties,&#xA;statutory or otherwise, so the above exclusions may not apply to Licensee.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;10. LIMITATIONS ON LIABILITY. PRAMATI&apos;S LICENSORS SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR DIRECT DAMAGES&#xA;OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER UNDER THIS AGREEMENT. UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL&#xA;PRAMATI, ITS SUBSIDIARIES OR ANY OF ITS LICENSORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOSS OR&#xA;INACCURACY OF DATA, LOSS OF PROFITS OR INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL&#xA;OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES, EVEN IF SUCH PARTY HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF&#xA;SUCH DAMAGES. TOTAL LIABILITY, IF ANY, ARISING OUT OF THIS AGREEMENT OR LICENSEE&apos;S USE&#xA;OF THE SOFTWARE OR RELATED SERVICES SHALL EXCEED THE FEES PAID BY LICENSEE FOR THE&#xA;AFFECTED SOFTWARE OR RELATED SERVICE(S) GIVING RISE TO THE CLAIM. THE FOREGOING&#xA;RESTRICTIONS, DISCLAIMERS AND LIMITATIONS SHALL REMAIN IN FORCE EVEN IN THE EVENT OF A&#xA;FUNDAMENTAL BREACH BY PRAMATI OR A BREACH BY PRAMATI OF A CONDITION OR&#xA;FUNDAMENTAL TERM HEREUNDER. Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion or limitation of indirect,&#xA;special, incidental, consequential or exemplary damages or the limitation of liability to specified amounts, so&#xA;the above limitations or exclusions may not apply to Licensee. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;10.1 Licensee acknowledges that Pramati has no knowledge of, or control over, the installation or use of the&#xA;Software by Licensee. Licensee agrees to defend, indemnify and hold Pramati harmless with respect to any&#xA;suit, claim or proceeding brought against Pramati alleging that installation or use by, or under authority of,&#xA;Licensee of the Software caused personal injury, property damage, or economic loss.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;11. GOVERNING LAW; COMPLETE AGREEMENT. This Agreement shall be construed and enforced in&#xA;accordance with the laws of the State of California, United States of America. The parties agree that venue for&#xA;any dispute under this Agreement shall be San Mateo County, California, U.S.A.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;12. AUDIT RIGHTS.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;12.1 Licensee shall keep accurate records of all activity with respect to use of the Software by Licensee,&#xA;including, without limitation, all Editions of Software used and the number of Named Users accessing the&#xA;Software or the number of CPUs. Licensee shall provide Pramati with summaries of such records upon&#xA;request. At any time during the term of this Agreement, Pramati shall have the right to audit Licensee&apos;s records&#xA;in order to verify that Licensee is limiting use of the Software in accordance with this Agreement. If any audit&#xA;reveals that Licensee is not limiting use of the Software in accordance with this Agreement, Licensee shall&#xA;pay Pramati any underpaid license fees at Pramati&apos;s then current rates within five days of notification of such&#xA;underpayment. If any audit reveals that Licensee has underpaid Pramati by an amount equal to or greater than&#xA;five percent of applicable license fees, Licensee shall also reimburse Pramati for the costs associated with the&#xA;audit.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;13. NOTICES. All notices or other communications required to be given under this Agreement shall be in&#xA;writing and delivered either personally or by mail via an internationally recognized governmental or private mail&#xA;service, certified, return receipt requested, postage prepaid, and addressed as provided in this Agreement or&#xA;as otherwise requested by the receiving party. Notices delivered personally shall be effective upon delivery and&#xA;notices delivered by mail shall be effective upon their receipt by the party to whom they are addressed.&#xA;Licensee shall address all correspondence regarding this Agreement to the Company Secretary of Pramati&#xA;Technologies (P) Ltd. at the Hyderabad, India Office whose address is available at www.pramati.com.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;14. ENTIRE AGREEMENT; MODIFICATIONS AND WAIVERS. This Agreement constitutes the full and entire&#xA;understanding and agreement between the parties with regard to the subjects hereof.  No term of this&#xA;Agreement may be modified except by a writing signed by an authorized representative of each of the parties.&#xA;A waiver by a party of its rights under this Agreement shall not be binding unless contained in a writing signed&#xA;by an authorized representative of the party waiving its rights. The non-enforcement or waiver of any provision&#xA;on one (1) occasion shall not constitute a waiver of such provision on any other occasions unless expressly so&#xA;agreed in writing. It is agreed that no use of trade or other regular practice or method of dealing between the&#xA;parties hereto shall be used to modify, interpret, supplement, or alter in any manner the terms of this&#xA;Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;15. SEVERABILITY. In the event that any provision of this Agreement is found invalid or unenforceable pursuant&#xA;to judicial decree or decision, the remainder of this Agreement shall remain valid and enforceable according to&#xA;its terms.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;16. FORCE MAJEURE. No party shall be responsible for any failure to perform due to unforeseen&#xA;circumstances or to causes beyond the party&apos;s reasonable control, including but not limited to acts of God,&#xA;war, riot, embargoes, acts of civil or military authorities, fire, floods, accidents, strikes, or shortages of&#xA;transportation, facilities, fuel, energy, labor, or materials. In the event of any such delay, a party may defer any&#xA;delivery dates for a period equal to the time of such delay. Notwithstanding the foregoing, if a party is in default&#xA;under this Section for more than fifteen (15) days, the non-defaulting party may terminate this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;17. ARBITRATION. Any controversy or claim arising out of or relating to this Agreement, or the breach thereof&#xA;shall be settled by binding arbitration in the County of San Mateo, California, administered by the American&#xA;Arbitration Association in accordance with its then current Commercial Arbitration Rules, and judgment on the&#xA;award rendered by the arbitrator may be entered in any court having jurisdiction thereof. The arbitrator may&#xA;award monetary damages, punitive damages, injunctive relief, rescission, restitution, costs and attorneys&apos;&#xA;fees. The arbitration award shall be final and binding regardless of whether one of the parties fails or refuses to&#xA;participate in the arbitration. The arbitrator shall not have the power to amend this Agreement in any respect.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;18. ATTORNEYS&apos; FEES. In the event of any dispute with respect to this Agreement, the prevailing party shall&#xA;be entitled to reasonable attorneys&apos; fees and other costs and expenses incurred in resolving such dispute.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;19. TAXES. Unless otherwise agreed between Consultant and Company, Consultant and Company shall each&#xA;have sole responsibility for collecting, reporting, and/or paying all income, sales, excise, property, value-added&#xA;tax, and other taxes imposed by any governmental authority as they pertain to Consultant&apos;s and Company&apos;s&#xA;respective duties, obligations, and performance hereunder.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20. DEFINITIONS.&#xA;&#xA;As used herein, the terms set forth below shall have the following respective meanings:&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.1 &quot;Documentation&quot; means the publications prepared and delivered to Licensee by Pramati that accompanies&#xA;the Software, such as reference, user, installation, systems administrator and technical guides. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.2 &quot;CPU&quot; means each central processing unit designated for use on a specific computing device.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.3 &quot;Software&quot; shall mean the machine readable object code, delivered by Pramati, to Licensee and may&#xA;include software licensed from third parties, together with other software and/or other products subsequently&#xA;delivered to Licensee by Pramati and all updates and upgrades of the same provided to Licensee by Pramati&#xA;and/or its suppliers. Software includes &quot;Server Software&quot; including current release(s) of Pramati Server and&#xA;Pramati Message Server and &quot;Studio Software&quot; including current release(s) of Pramati Studio and &quot;Plugin&#xA;Software&quot;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.4 &quot;Pramati&quot; shall mean Pramati Technologies (P) Limited, as incorporated in the State of Andhra Pradesh,&#xA;India, under Companies Act, 1956, whose address can be found at Pramati&apos;s website at www.pramati.com.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.5 &quot;Licensee&quot; shall mean the entity or individual, either on the individual&apos; s behalf or on behalf of the entity that&#xA;individual represents, who installs the Software or otherwise agrees to be bound by the terms and conditions&#xA;contained in this Agreement. Further, each individual representing an entity represents and warrants that&#xA;he/she has the authority to bind the entity to this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.6 &quot;Named Users&quot; shall mean an individual or individuals employed by Licensee who is/are authorized to use&#xA;the software. The number of licenses for the Program must equal the total number of Named Users.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.7 &quot;Application&quot; shall mean machine-readable object code provided by &quot;Application Provider&quot; to Licensee&#xA;which may be deployed on Software.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.8 &quot;Edition&quot; shall mean either the Standard Edition or the Enterprise Edition of the Software.  The Standard&#xA;Edition does not allow use of certain features available in the Enterprise Edition.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;BY CLICKING THE &quot;ACCEPT&quot; BUTTON OR CHECKING THE &quot;ACCEPT&quot; CHECK-BOX DURING&#xA;INSTALLATION OF THE SOFTWARE, LICENSEE IS AGREEING TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND&#xA;CONDITIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT.&#xA;'/>
        <property name='df_LT.copyright' value='Copyright © 2008 Pramati Technologies. All Rights Reserved.'/>
        <property name='df_LT.featureName' value='Pramati Server 6.0 Plugin'/>
        <property name='df_LT.description' value='Supported server versions 4.1, 5.0 and 6.0'/>
        <property name='df_LT.providerName' value='Pramati Technologies'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='2'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.group' version='2.1.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.localization' name='df_LT' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='2'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.jst.server' range='[2.1.0,2.1.0]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.jar' range='[2.1.0,2.1.0]'>
          <filter>
            (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
          </filter>
        </required>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='%25licenseURL' url='%25licenseURL'>
          %license
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        %copyright
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.group' version='2.2.0' singleton='false'>
      <update id='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.group' range='[0.0.0,2.2.0)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='9'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%featureName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='%description'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%providerName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.group' value='true'/>
        <property name='df_LT.license' value='PRAMATI SOFTWARE END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;THIS IS A LICENSE AND NOT A SALE&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;This License Agreement (&quot;Agreement&quot;) is a legal agreement between Pramati Technologies (P) Ltd. (&quot;Pramati&quot;)&#xA;and the end user licensing the Software and Documentation under this Agreement (&quot;Licensee&quot;). By installing&#xA;the Pramati Server, Pramati Message Server (&quot;Server Software&quot;) and/or Pramati Studio (&quot;Studio Software&quot;) &#xA;and/or Pramati Server Plug-in (&quot;Plugin Software&quot;) (collectively &quot;Software&quot;) Licensee agrees to be bound by the &#xA;terms and conditions set forth in this Agreement. In the event Licensee does not wish to be bound to the terms &#xA;of this Agreement, Licensee must promptly return the Software and Documentation to Pramati together with&#xA;proof of purchase in the manner set forth in Pramati&apos;s return policy found on www.pramati.com in order to &#xA;receive a full refund. All returns must comply.  This Agreement applies to any subsequent purchases of the &#xA;Software or Documentation. Licensee must notify all Named Users of the Software of the terms and conditions &#xA;of this Agreement. The Software is licensed to Licensee, not sold.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;LICENSEE MAY USE THE ENCLOSED SOFTWARE AND DOCUMENTATION ONLY IN ACCORDANCE &#xA;WITH THIS AGREEMENT (UNLESS LICENSEE HAS ALREADY SIGNED A VALID LICENSE AGREEMENT&#xA;WITH PRAMATI OR ONE OF ITS SUBSIDIARIES TO USE THE SOFTWARE).&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.&#x9;LICENSE TERMS. Pramati grants to Licensee, and Licensee accepts from Pramati, a limited non-exclusive&#xA;license to install and use the Software and Documentation in accordance with the applicable License Type set&#xA;forth in Section 1.3, below. All rights not specifically granted to Licensee in this Agreement are retained by&#xA;Pramati and its licensors. Licensee shall not allow the use of the Software except on equipment owned or&#xA;leased by Licensee for Licensee&apos;s business purposes and only by the number of authorized users, as&#xA;applicable for the License Type. Licensee shall not allow the unauthorized use of the Software and&#xA;Documentation and will notify Pramati and pay any additional fees pursuant to Pramati&apos;s then current price list&#xA;before making expanded use of the Software.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.1&#x9;License Key. Pramati provides you with a license key which will give you access to the Software in&#xA;accordance with the applicable License Type Licensee has ordered (&quot;License Key&quot;). Licensee will only receive&#xA;a License Key for an Evaluation License, should Licensee wish to purchase a license after the evaluation&#xA;period Pramati will then provide Licensee with the appropriate License Certificate. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.2&#x9;In addition, Pramati will provide Licensee with a certificate of use, except in the case of an Evaluation&#xA;License or a Development License, which sets forth with specificity the licenses granted to you under this&#xA;Agreement (&quot;License Certificate&quot;). The License Certificate is either sent with this Agreement, or separately by&#xA;electronic mail, or when Licensee downloads the Evaluation License or Developer License and is incorporated&#xA;by reference into this Agreement. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3&#x9;&quot;License Type&quot; for Software shall mean any one of the purposes set forth below for which the Software&#xA;(whether Server Software or Studio Software or Plugin Software, as applicable) has been licensed under this&#xA;Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.1&#x9;&quot;Evaluation License&quot; grants Licensee a thirty (30) day, restricted non-exclusive license to install and use&#xA;the Software subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement. Licensee agrees to use the Software&#xA;under such license solely for evaluation purposes. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.2&#x9;&quot;Deployment License&quot; grants Licensee a non-exclusive license to install and use the Software, limited&#xA;only by the Edition and number of CPUs set forth in the License Certificate for deployment with an unlimited&#xA;number of Licensee&apos;s applications subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.3&#x9;&quot;Production License&quot; grants Licensee a non-exclusive license to install and use the Studio Software,&#xA;limited only by number of Named Users set forth in the License Certificate subject to the terms and provisions&#xA;of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.4&#x9;&quot;Development License&quot; grants Licensee a one hundred eighty (180) day, restricted non-exclusive license&#xA;for the number of developers in Licensee&apos;s organization set forth in the License Certificate to install and use&#xA;the Software solely for Licensee&apos;s internal software application development purposes only and not for any&#xA;other purpose subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement. Licensee may use the media on which&#xA;the Software resides to copy the Software onto those computing devices used by Named Users. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.5&#x9;&quot;Limited License&quot; grants Licensee a restricted non-exclusive license to install and use the Software,&#xA;limited by the Edition and number of CPUs set forth in the License Certificate. Licensee may install and use&#xA;Software for deployment of only a specific named Application developed by Application Provider as set forth in&#xA;the License Certificate subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.6&#x9;&quot;Education License&quot; grants Licensee a one hundred eighty (180) day restricted non-exclusive license to&#xA;install and use the Software, limited by the Edition and restricted by the number of Named Users as set forth in&#xA;the License Certificate solely for the purposes of education, training or academic research subject to the terms&#xA;and provisions of this Agreement. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;2. FEES AND PAYMENT. This is a fee bearing license, Pramati&apos;s current license fees are listed at&#xA;www.pramati.com, All fees resulting from this Agreement are due and payable on Licensee&apos;s receipt of the&#xA;invoice if related to a product or Support Service(s) (as defined in Section 3 below) acquired directly from&#xA;Pramati; otherwise such fees are due and payable in accordance with the applicable authorized reseller&apos;s&#xA;policies. Licensee shall pay all applicable shipping charges, and sales, use, value-added, personal property,&#xA;consumption or similar taxes, tariffs or governmental charges, exclusive of Pramati&apos;s or its reseller&apos;s net&#xA;income and corporate franchise taxes.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;3. SUPPORT SERVICES. Licensee may purchase technical telephone support, update assurance and/or&#xA;training services in support of the Software (&quot;Support Service(s)&quot;) pursuant to a separate support agreement&#xA;and in accordance with then-current plans for such Support Service(s), current versions of which can be found&#xA;within Pramati&apos;s website at &quot;www.pramati.com&quot;. Upgrades will be distributed to Licensee in accordance with&#xA;Pramati&apos;s then current maintenance and support fees, terms and conditions.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;4. RESTRICTIONS AND OTHER CONDITIONS.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(a)&#x9;Except as set forth in Section 4(e) below, Licensee may not copy the Software or Documentation.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(b)&#x9;Licensee may not modify, enhance, reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble, supplement, create&#xA;derivative work from, adapt, translate or otherwise reduce the Software to human readable form (except as&#xA;specifically permitted in the Documentation). Notwithstanding the foregoing, in the event Licensee is located in&#xA;the European Economic Area and there is a legal requirement in this area to have access to the source code&#xA;of the Software to achieve interoperability of the Software with other software, Licensee shall notify Pramati&#xA;and Pramati can at its sole option choose to either (i) perform the work in order to achieve such interoperability&#xA;at its then-standard rates for such work to Licensee or (ii) to permit Licensee to reverse engineer parts of the&#xA;Software in order to obtain such source code, but only to the extent necessary to achieve such interoperability.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(c)&#x9;Licensee may not rent or lease the Software to third parties, nor allow use of the Software for service&#xA;bureau, timesharing, application service provider or any other form of shared use.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(d)&#x9;Except as otherwise expressly permitted in this Agreement, Licensee may not cause or permit the&#xA;disclosure, copying, renting, licensing, sublicensing, leasing, dissemination or other distribution of the&#xA;Software or its Documentation by any means or in any form to any third party including, without limitation, any&#xA;form of distributor or reseller without a signed agreement with Pramati granting such right(s).&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(e)&#x9;Licensee may make one copy of the Software and Documentation solely for archival, emergency back-up,&#xA;or disaster recovery purposes; provided, however, that all copyright and other proprietary notices of Pramati and&#xA;its licensors are reproduced on such copies.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(f)&#x9;Licensee acknowledges that, although the Software media may contain other software products, Licensee is&#xA;hereby licensed to install and use only the Software designated by the License Key and the License&#xA;Certificate provided to Licensee for operation of the Software.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(g)&#x9;The Software may not be transferred, sold, assigned or otherwise conveyed (whether by operation of law&#xA;or otherwise) to another party or outside the country in which it was originally delivered to Licensee without&#xA;Pramati&apos;s prior written consent subject to Licensee&apos;s compliance with all applicable export and re-export&#xA;regulations and restrictions; provided, however, that if Licensee is located in the European Economic Area, and&#xA;is a legal requirement in this area, Licensee may transfer Licensee&apos;s copy of the Software together with its&#xA;Documentation on a permanent basis, so long as Licensee notifies Pramati as to the name and address of the&#xA;recipient of Licensee&apos;s copy and that such recipient agrees in writing to be bound by the terms and conditions&#xA;of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(h)&#x9;Results of benchmark or other performance tests run on the Software may not be disclosed to any third&#xA;party without Pramati&apos;s prior written consent.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(i)&#x9;The Software contains software programs written in Java. The Software is not fault-tolerant and is not&#xA;designed, manufactured or intended for use or resale in the on-line control, design, construction, operation or&#xA;maintenance of any nuclear facilities, aircraft navigation or communication systems, air traffic control, direct&#xA;life support machines, or weapons systems, in which the failure of the Software could lead directly to death,&#xA;personal injury, or severe physical or environmental damage (&quot;High Risk Activities&quot;). Pramati and its suppliers&#xA;specifically disclaim any express or implied warranty of fitness for High Risk Activities. Licensee agrees that it&#xA;is not licensed to use the Software for High Risk Activities and that failure to comply with this section will result&#xA;in immediate termination of this Agreement without refund.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(j)&#x9;Third party software products supplied with the Software are provided to Licensee subject to such third&#xA;party&apos;s license agreement with Pramati, the terms of which may change from time to time. The Cloudscape&#xA;software products may only be used as a part of Pramati&apos;s development Software. The Cloudscape software&#xA;products may only be used on the operating system platforms on which Informix has made the Cloudscape&#xA;software generally commercially available. Licensee may not copy, distribute, or otherwise deploy the&#xA;Cloudscape software products or any other programs developed using such Cloudscape software. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;GENERAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;5. COPYRIGHT AND OWNERSHIP. Title, ownership rights, and all intellectual property rights in and to the&#xA;Software and Documentation including all copies thereof, and all rights therein including, but not limited to, all&#xA;trade secrets, trademarks, patents, copyrights, trade secrets and moral rights shall remain the sole and&#xA;exclusive property of Pramati and/or its licensors. Licensee acknowledges that the Software contains valuable&#xA;confidential information and trade secrets of Pramati and/or its licensors. No title or ownership to the Software&#xA;or Documentation or any part or modification thereof is transferred to Licensee. Software is protected by&#xA;copyright laws and international treaty provisions. Licensee shall not remove or alter Pramati&apos;s or any third&#xA;party&apos; s ownership, trademark, copyright, or other proprietary notices on the Software or Documentation.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;5.1 Pramati acknowledges that Software contains third-party software as listed in the attached files.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;5.2 Licensee acknowledges that Software contains software from third-party and agrees to abide by the&#xA;third-party agreements attached hereto. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;6. U.S. GOVERNMENT RIGHTS. If the Software or its Documentation is acquired by or on behalf of the United&#xA;States Government, the United States Government agrees that such Software and Documentation is&#xA;&quot;commercial computer software&quot; or &quot;commercial computer software documentation&quot; and that use,&#xA;modification, duplication and disclosure of the Software and its Documentation by the United States&#xA;Government is subject to restrictions set forth in this Agreement or in a written agreement to the contrary&#xA;specifying the United States Government&apos;s right to use the Software and its Documentation, pursuant to FAR&#xA;§ 12.212(a) and/or DFARS § 227.7202-1(a), as applicable. Pramati reserves all unpublished rights under U.S.&#xA;copyright laws.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;7. TERM OF LICENSE. Either party may terminate this Agreement if the other party materially breaches any of&#xA;its obligations hereunder and fails to cure such breach within thirty (30) days after written notice. Upon&#xA;termination, all rights granted to Licensee hereunder shall terminate and Licensee shall cease using the&#xA;Software, and within five (5) days of termination Licensee shall destroy or return to Pramati all copies of the&#xA;Software and its Documentation in any form. Upon request, Licensee shall certify that all copies of the&#xA;Software have been destroyed. Termination of this Agreement will not affect any provisions relating to the&#xA;payment of amounts due, limiting or disclaiming Pramati&apos;s liability, confidentiality, and ownership of copyrights&#xA;and other intellectual property of Pramati including, but not limited to, the Software and Documentation, which&#xA;provisions will survive termination of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;8. CONFIDENTIALITY.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;8.1 Definition. Licensee agrees that information disclosed to it by Pramati including, but not limited to,&#xA;information learned or developed using the Software or Documentation, or that relates to its products, designs,&#xA;research, development, know-how, or third party confidential information, will be considered and referred to &#xA;collectively in this Agreement as &quot;Confidential Information.&quot; Confidential Information, however, does not include&#xA;information that 1) is now or subsequently becomes generally available to the public through no fault or breach&#xA;on the part of Licensee; 2) Licensee can demonstrate to have had rightfully in its possession prior to&#xA;disclosure by Pramati of such Confidential Information; 3) is independently developed by Licensee without the&#xA;use of any Confidential Information, the Software or Documentation of Pramati; or 4) Licensee rightfully obtains&#xA;from a third party who has the right to transfer or disclose it.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;8.2 Nondisclosure and Nonuse of Confidential Information. Except as otherwise set forth in this Agreement,&#xA;Licensee agrees that it will not disclosure, publish, or disseminate Confidential Information of Pramati to&#xA;anyone other than those of its employees with a demonstrated need to know, and Licensee agrees to take all&#xA;reasonable precautions to prevent any unauthorized use, disclosure, publication, or dissemination of&#xA;Confidential Information. Licensee agrees to use any Confidential Information disclosed to it solely for the&#xA;purposes contemplated by this Agreement and not otherwise for its own or any third party&apos;s benefit without the&#xA;prior written approval of an authorized representative of Pramati in each instance. All Confidential Information&#xA;remains the property of Pramati. Licensee shall enter into appropriate agreements, if Licensee has not already&#xA;done so, to protect the Confidential Information. Licensee shall not use Confidential Information at any time for&#xA;any purpose other than as authorized by Pramati.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;9. LIMITED WARRANTY. For a period of thirty (30) days from the date of Licensee&apos;s receipt of the Software,&#xA;Pramati warrants that the Software, when properly installed and used with the equipment configuration and in&#xA;the operating environment specified by Pramati, will operate in all material respects in conformity with its&#xA;Documentation, and the Software media shall be free of defects. Pramati warrants that Software telephone&#xA;support and training services (&quot;Related Service(s)&quot;) will be performed by qualified personnel in a professional&#xA;manner. In the event of non-conforming Software or Related Service(s), or if the media is defective, Licensee&apos;s&#xA;sole remedy and Pramati&apos;s exclusive liability shall be, as applicable and at Pramati&apos;s option, replacement of&#xA;the affected Software or media, or re-performance of the Related Service(s) at no additional charge, or a refund&#xA;of the fees paid for the affected Software or Related Service(s). EVALUATION SOFTWARE AND ANY THIRD&#xA;PARTY SOFTWARE ARE PROVIDED TO LICENSEE &quot;AS IS&quot; WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY, EXPRESS OR&#xA;IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE. PRAMATI DISCLAIMS ALL OTHER WARRANTIES AND&#xA;CONDITIONS, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION&#xA;THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND&#xA;WHETHER ARISING BY STATUTE OR IN LAW OR AS A RESULT OF A COURSE OF DEALING OR&#xA;USAGE OF TRADE, WITH RESPECT TO THE SOFTWARE, ITS DOCUMENTATION, SUPPORT OR OTHER&#xA;SERVICES RELATED TO THE SOFTWARE. NO WARRANTY IS MADE REGARDING THE RESULTS OF&#xA;THE SOFTWARE OR RELATED SERVICES OR THAT ALL ERRORS IN THE SOFTWARE WILL BE&#xA;CORRECTED, OR THAT THE SOFTWARE&apos;S FUNCTIONALITY WILL MEET LICENSEE&apos;S REQUIREMENTS.&#xA;LICENSEE ACKNOWLEDGES LICENSEE&apos;S RESPONSIBILITY TO (i) REGULARLY BACK UP DATA&#xA;MAINTAINED ON ANY COMPUTER SYSTEM USING THE SOFTWARE AND (ii) ADEQUATELY TEST&#xA;PRIOR TO DEPLOYMENT EACH PRODUCTION VERSION OF THE SOFTWARE IN A CONFIGURATION&#xA;WHICH REASONABLY SIMULATES LICENSEE&apos;S PLANNED DEPLOYMENT OR PRODUCTION&#xA;ENVIRONMENT. This limited warranty gives Licensee specific legal rights. Licensee may have other rights that&#xA;vary among jurisdictions. Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of implied conditions or warranties,&#xA;statutory or otherwise, so the above exclusions may not apply to Licensee.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;10. LIMITATIONS ON LIABILITY. PRAMATI&apos;S LICENSORS SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR DIRECT DAMAGES&#xA;OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER UNDER THIS AGREEMENT. UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL&#xA;PRAMATI, ITS SUBSIDIARIES OR ANY OF ITS LICENSORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOSS OR&#xA;INACCURACY OF DATA, LOSS OF PROFITS OR INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL&#xA;OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES, EVEN IF SUCH PARTY HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF&#xA;SUCH DAMAGES. TOTAL LIABILITY, IF ANY, ARISING OUT OF THIS AGREEMENT OR LICENSEE&apos;S USE&#xA;OF THE SOFTWARE OR RELATED SERVICES SHALL EXCEED THE FEES PAID BY LICENSEE FOR THE&#xA;AFFECTED SOFTWARE OR RELATED SERVICE(S) GIVING RISE TO THE CLAIM. THE FOREGOING&#xA;RESTRICTIONS, DISCLAIMERS AND LIMITATIONS SHALL REMAIN IN FORCE EVEN IN THE EVENT OF A&#xA;FUNDAMENTAL BREACH BY PRAMATI OR A BREACH BY PRAMATI OF A CONDITION OR&#xA;FUNDAMENTAL TERM HEREUNDER. Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion or limitation of indirect,&#xA;special, incidental, consequential or exemplary damages or the limitation of liability to specified amounts, so&#xA;the above limitations or exclusions may not apply to Licensee. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;10.1 Licensee acknowledges that Pramati has no knowledge of, or control over, the installation or use of the&#xA;Software by Licensee. Licensee agrees to defend, indemnify and hold Pramati harmless with respect to any&#xA;suit, claim or proceeding brought against Pramati alleging that installation or use by, or under authority of,&#xA;Licensee of the Software caused personal injury, property damage, or economic loss.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;11. GOVERNING LAW; COMPLETE AGREEMENT. This Agreement shall be construed and enforced in&#xA;accordance with the laws of the State of California, United States of America. The parties agree that venue for&#xA;any dispute under this Agreement shall be San Mateo County, California, U.S.A.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;12. AUDIT RIGHTS.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;12.1 Licensee shall keep accurate records of all activity with respect to use of the Software by Licensee,&#xA;including, without limitation, all Editions of Software used and the number of Named Users accessing the&#xA;Software or the number of CPUs. Licensee shall provide Pramati with summaries of such records upon&#xA;request. At any time during the term of this Agreement, Pramati shall have the right to audit Licensee&apos;s records&#xA;in order to verify that Licensee is limiting use of the Software in accordance with this Agreement. If any audit&#xA;reveals that Licensee is not limiting use of the Software in accordance with this Agreement, Licensee shall&#xA;pay Pramati any underpaid license fees at Pramati&apos;s then current rates within five days of notification of such&#xA;underpayment. If any audit reveals that Licensee has underpaid Pramati by an amount equal to or greater than&#xA;five percent of applicable license fees, Licensee shall also reimburse Pramati for the costs associated with the&#xA;audit.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;13. NOTICES. All notices or other communications required to be given under this Agreement shall be in&#xA;writing and delivered either personally or by mail via an internationally recognized governmental or private mail&#xA;service, certified, return receipt requested, postage prepaid, and addressed as provided in this Agreement or&#xA;as otherwise requested by the receiving party. Notices delivered personally shall be effective upon delivery and&#xA;notices delivered by mail shall be effective upon their receipt by the party to whom they are addressed.&#xA;Licensee shall address all correspondence regarding this Agreement to the Company Secretary of Pramati&#xA;Technologies (P) Ltd. at the Hyderabad, India Office whose address is available at www.pramati.com.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;14. ENTIRE AGREEMENT; MODIFICATIONS AND WAIVERS. This Agreement constitutes the full and entire&#xA;understanding and agreement between the parties with regard to the subjects hereof.  No term of this&#xA;Agreement may be modified except by a writing signed by an authorized representative of each of the parties.&#xA;A waiver by a party of its rights under this Agreement shall not be binding unless contained in a writing signed&#xA;by an authorized representative of the party waiving its rights. The non-enforcement or waiver of any provision&#xA;on one (1) occasion shall not constitute a waiver of such provision on any other occasions unless expressly so&#xA;agreed in writing. It is agreed that no use of trade or other regular practice or method of dealing between the&#xA;parties hereto shall be used to modify, interpret, supplement, or alter in any manner the terms of this&#xA;Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;15. SEVERABILITY. In the event that any provision of this Agreement is found invalid or unenforceable pursuant&#xA;to judicial decree or decision, the remainder of this Agreement shall remain valid and enforceable according to&#xA;its terms.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;16. FORCE MAJEURE. No party shall be responsible for any failure to perform due to unforeseen&#xA;circumstances or to causes beyond the party&apos;s reasonable control, including but not limited to acts of God,&#xA;war, riot, embargoes, acts of civil or military authorities, fire, floods, accidents, strikes, or shortages of&#xA;transportation, facilities, fuel, energy, labor, or materials. In the event of any such delay, a party may defer any&#xA;delivery dates for a period equal to the time of such delay. Notwithstanding the foregoing, if a party is in default&#xA;under this Section for more than fifteen (15) days, the non-defaulting party may terminate this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;17. ARBITRATION. Any controversy or claim arising out of or relating to this Agreement, or the breach thereof&#xA;shall be settled by binding arbitration in the County of San Mateo, California, administered by the American&#xA;Arbitration Association in accordance with its then current Commercial Arbitration Rules, and judgment on the&#xA;award rendered by the arbitrator may be entered in any court having jurisdiction thereof. The arbitrator may&#xA;award monetary damages, punitive damages, injunctive relief, rescission, restitution, costs and attorneys&apos;&#xA;fees. The arbitration award shall be final and binding regardless of whether one of the parties fails or refuses to&#xA;participate in the arbitration. The arbitrator shall not have the power to amend this Agreement in any respect.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;18. ATTORNEYS&apos; FEES. In the event of any dispute with respect to this Agreement, the prevailing party shall&#xA;be entitled to reasonable attorneys&apos; fees and other costs and expenses incurred in resolving such dispute.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;19. TAXES. Unless otherwise agreed between Consultant and Company, Consultant and Company shall each&#xA;have sole responsibility for collecting, reporting, and/or paying all income, sales, excise, property, value-added&#xA;tax, and other taxes imposed by any governmental authority as they pertain to Consultant&apos;s and Company&apos;s&#xA;respective duties, obligations, and performance hereunder.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20. DEFINITIONS.&#xA;&#xA;As used herein, the terms set forth below shall have the following respective meanings:&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.1 &quot;Documentation&quot; means the publications prepared and delivered to Licensee by Pramati that accompanies&#xA;the Software, such as reference, user, installation, systems administrator and technical guides. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.2 &quot;CPU&quot; means each central processing unit designated for use on a specific computing device.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.3 &quot;Software&quot; shall mean the machine readable object code, delivered by Pramati, to Licensee and may&#xA;include software licensed from third parties, together with other software and/or other products subsequently&#xA;delivered to Licensee by Pramati and all updates and upgrades of the same provided to Licensee by Pramati&#xA;and/or its suppliers. Software includes &quot;Server Software&quot; including current release(s) of Pramati Server and&#xA;Pramati Message Server and &quot;Studio Software&quot; including current release(s) of Pramati Studio and &quot;Plugin&#xA;Software&quot;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.4 &quot;Pramati&quot; shall mean Pramati Technologies (P) Limited, as incorporated in the State of Andhra Pradesh,&#xA;India, under Companies Act, 1956, whose address can be found at Pramati&apos;s website at www.pramati.com.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.5 &quot;Licensee&quot; shall mean the entity or individual, either on the individual&apos; s behalf or on behalf of the entity that&#xA;individual represents, who installs the Software or otherwise agrees to be bound by the terms and conditions&#xA;contained in this Agreement. Further, each individual representing an entity represents and warrants that&#xA;he/she has the authority to bind the entity to this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.6 &quot;Named Users&quot; shall mean an individual or individuals employed by Licensee who is/are authorized to use&#xA;the software. The number of licenses for the Program must equal the total number of Named Users.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.7 &quot;Application&quot; shall mean machine-readable object code provided by &quot;Application Provider&quot; to Licensee&#xA;which may be deployed on Software.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.8 &quot;Edition&quot; shall mean either the Standard Edition or the Enterprise Edition of the Software.  The Standard&#xA;Edition does not allow use of certain features available in the Enterprise Edition.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;BY CLICKING THE &quot;ACCEPT&quot; BUTTON OR CHECKING THE &quot;ACCEPT&quot; CHECK-BOX DURING&#xA;INSTALLATION OF THE SOFTWARE, LICENSEE IS AGREEING TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND&#xA;CONDITIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT.&#xA;'/>
        <property name='df_LT.copyright' value='Copyright © 2008 Pramati Technologies. All Rights Reserved.'/>
        <property name='df_LT.featureName' value='Pramati Server 6.5 Plugin'/>
        <property name='df_LT.description' value='Supported server versions 4.1, 5.0, 6.0 and 6.5'/>
        <property name='df_LT.providerName' value='Pramati Technologies'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='2'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.group' version='2.2.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.localization' name='df_LT' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='2'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.jst.server' range='[2.2.0,2.2.0]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.jar' range='[2.2.0,2.2.0]'>
          <filter>
            (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
          </filter>
        </required>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='%25licenseURL' url='%25licenseURL'>
          %license
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        %copyright
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.group' version='1.0.1' singleton='false'>
      <update id='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.group' range='[0.0.0,1.0.1)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='5'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='com.pramati.eclipse.feature'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='[Enter Feature Description here.]'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description.url' value='http://www.pramati.com/description'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='Pramati'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.group' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='1'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.group' version='1.0.1'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='2'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.jst.server' range='[1.0.1,1.0.1]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.jar' range='[1.0.1,1.0.1]'>
          <filter>
            (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
          </filter>
        </required>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='http://www.pramati.com/license' url='http://www.pramati.com/license'>
          []
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright uri='http://www.pramati.com/copyright' url='http://www.pramati.com/copyright'>
        [Enter Copyright Description here.]
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.group' version='2.0.0' singleton='false'>
      <update id='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.group' range='[0.0.0,2.0.0)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='9'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%featureName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='%description'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%providerName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.group' value='true'/>
        <property name='df_LT.license' value='PRAMATI SOFTWARE END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;THIS IS A LICENSE AND NOT A SALE&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;This License Agreement (&quot;Agreement&quot;) is a legal agreement between Pramati Technologies (P) Ltd. (&quot;Pramati&quot;)&#xA;and the end user licensing the Software and Documentation under this Agreement (&quot;Licensee&quot;). By installing&#xA;the Pramati Server, Pramati Message Server (&quot;Server Software&quot;) and/or Pramati Studio (&quot;Studio Software&quot;) &#xA;and/or Pramati Server Plug-in (&quot;Plugin Software&quot;) (collectively &quot;Software&quot;) Licensee agrees to be bound by the &#xA;terms and conditions set forth in this Agreement. In the event Licensee does not wish to be bound to the terms &#xA;of this Agreement, Licensee must promptly return the Software and Documentation to Pramati together with&#xA;proof of purchase in the manner set forth in Pramati&apos;s return policy found on www.pramati.com in order to &#xA;receive a full refund. All returns must comply.  This Agreement applies to any subsequent purchases of the &#xA;Software or Documentation. Licensee must notify all Named Users of the Software of the terms and conditions &#xA;of this Agreement. The Software is licensed to Licensee, not sold.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;LICENSEE MAY USE THE ENCLOSED SOFTWARE AND DOCUMENTATION ONLY IN ACCORDANCE &#xA;WITH THIS AGREEMENT (UNLESS LICENSEE HAS ALREADY SIGNED A VALID LICENSE AGREEMENT&#xA;WITH PRAMATI OR ONE OF ITS SUBSIDIARIES TO USE THE SOFTWARE).&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.&#x9;LICENSE TERMS. Pramati grants to Licensee, and Licensee accepts from Pramati, a limited non-exclusive&#xA;license to install and use the Software and Documentation in accordance with the applicable License Type set&#xA;forth in Section 1.3, below. All rights not specifically granted to Licensee in this Agreement are retained by&#xA;Pramati and its licensors. Licensee shall not allow the use of the Software except on equipment owned or&#xA;leased by Licensee for Licensee&apos;s business purposes and only by the number of authorized users, as&#xA;applicable for the License Type. Licensee shall not allow the unauthorized use of the Software and&#xA;Documentation and will notify Pramati and pay any additional fees pursuant to Pramati&apos;s then current price list&#xA;before making expanded use of the Software.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.1&#x9;License Key. Pramati provides you with a license key which will give you access to the Software in&#xA;accordance with the applicable License Type Licensee has ordered (&quot;License Key&quot;). Licensee will only receive&#xA;a License Key for an Evaluation License, should Licensee wish to purchase a license after the evaluation&#xA;period Pramati will then provide Licensee with the appropriate License Certificate. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.2&#x9;In addition, Pramati will provide Licensee with a certificate of use, except in the case of an Evaluation&#xA;License or a Development License, which sets forth with specificity the licenses granted to you under this&#xA;Agreement (&quot;License Certificate&quot;). The License Certificate is either sent with this Agreement, or separately by&#xA;electronic mail, or when Licensee downloads the Evaluation License or Developer License and is incorporated&#xA;by reference into this Agreement. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3&#x9;&quot;License Type&quot; for Software shall mean any one of the purposes set forth below for which the Software&#xA;(whether Server Software or Studio Software or Plugin Software, as applicable) has been licensed under this&#xA;Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.1&#x9;&quot;Evaluation License&quot; grants Licensee a thirty (30) day, restricted non-exclusive license to install and use&#xA;the Software subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement. Licensee agrees to use the Software&#xA;under such license solely for evaluation purposes. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.2&#x9;&quot;Deployment License&quot; grants Licensee a non-exclusive license to install and use the Software, limited&#xA;only by the Edition and number of CPUs set forth in the License Certificate for deployment with an unlimited&#xA;number of Licensee&apos;s applications subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.3&#x9;&quot;Production License&quot; grants Licensee a non-exclusive license to install and use the Studio Software,&#xA;limited only by number of Named Users set forth in the License Certificate subject to the terms and provisions&#xA;of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.4&#x9;&quot;Development License&quot; grants Licensee a one hundred eighty (180) day, restricted non-exclusive license&#xA;for the number of developers in Licensee&apos;s organization set forth in the License Certificate to install and use&#xA;the Software solely for Licensee&apos;s internal software application development purposes only and not for any&#xA;other purpose subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement. Licensee may use the media on which&#xA;the Software resides to copy the Software onto those computing devices used by Named Users. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.5&#x9;&quot;Limited License&quot; grants Licensee a restricted non-exclusive license to install and use the Software,&#xA;limited by the Edition and number of CPUs set forth in the License Certificate. Licensee may install and use&#xA;Software for deployment of only a specific named Application developed by Application Provider as set forth in&#xA;the License Certificate subject to the terms and provisions of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;1.3.6&#x9;&quot;Education License&quot; grants Licensee a one hundred eighty (180) day restricted non-exclusive license to&#xA;install and use the Software, limited by the Edition and restricted by the number of Named Users as set forth in&#xA;the License Certificate solely for the purposes of education, training or academic research subject to the terms&#xA;and provisions of this Agreement. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;2. FEES AND PAYMENT. This is a fee bearing license, Pramati&apos;s current license fees are listed at&#xA;www.pramati.com, All fees resulting from this Agreement are due and payable on Licensee&apos;s receipt of the&#xA;invoice if related to a product or Support Service(s) (as defined in Section 3 below) acquired directly from&#xA;Pramati; otherwise such fees are due and payable in accordance with the applicable authorized reseller&apos;s&#xA;policies. Licensee shall pay all applicable shipping charges, and sales, use, value-added, personal property,&#xA;consumption or similar taxes, tariffs or governmental charges, exclusive of Pramati&apos;s or its reseller&apos;s net&#xA;income and corporate franchise taxes.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;3. SUPPORT SERVICES. Licensee may purchase technical telephone support, update assurance and/or&#xA;training services in support of the Software (&quot;Support Service(s)&quot;) pursuant to a separate support agreement&#xA;and in accordance with then-current plans for such Support Service(s), current versions of which can be found&#xA;within Pramati&apos;s website at &quot;www.pramati.com&quot;. Upgrades will be distributed to Licensee in accordance with&#xA;Pramati&apos;s then current maintenance and support fees, terms and conditions.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;4. RESTRICTIONS AND OTHER CONDITIONS.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(a)&#x9;Except as set forth in Section 4(e) below, Licensee may not copy the Software or Documentation.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(b)&#x9;Licensee may not modify, enhance, reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble, supplement, create&#xA;derivative work from, adapt, translate or otherwise reduce the Software to human readable form (except as&#xA;specifically permitted in the Documentation). Notwithstanding the foregoing, in the event Licensee is located in&#xA;the European Economic Area and there is a legal requirement in this area to have access to the source code&#xA;of the Software to achieve interoperability of the Software with other software, Licensee shall notify Pramati&#xA;and Pramati can at its sole option choose to either (i) perform the work in order to achieve such interoperability&#xA;at its then-standard rates for such work to Licensee or (ii) to permit Licensee to reverse engineer parts of the&#xA;Software in order to obtain such source code, but only to the extent necessary to achieve such interoperability.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(c)&#x9;Licensee may not rent or lease the Software to third parties, nor allow use of the Software for service&#xA;bureau, timesharing, application service provider or any other form of shared use.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(d)&#x9;Except as otherwise expressly permitted in this Agreement, Licensee may not cause or permit the&#xA;disclosure, copying, renting, licensing, sublicensing, leasing, dissemination or other distribution of the&#xA;Software or its Documentation by any means or in any form to any third party including, without limitation, any&#xA;form of distributor or reseller without a signed agreement with Pramati granting such right(s).&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(e)&#x9;Licensee may make one copy of the Software and Documentation solely for archival, emergency back-up,&#xA;or disaster recovery purposes; provided, however, that all copyright and other proprietary notices of Pramati and&#xA;its licensors are reproduced on such copies.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(f)&#x9;Licensee acknowledges that, although the Software media may contain other software products, Licensee is&#xA;hereby licensed to install and use only the Software designated by the License Key and the License&#xA;Certificate provided to Licensee for operation of the Software.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(g)&#x9;The Software may not be transferred, sold, assigned or otherwise conveyed (whether by operation of law&#xA;or otherwise) to another party or outside the country in which it was originally delivered to Licensee without&#xA;Pramati&apos;s prior written consent subject to Licensee&apos;s compliance with all applicable export and re-export&#xA;regulations and restrictions; provided, however, that if Licensee is located in the European Economic Area, and&#xA;is a legal requirement in this area, Licensee may transfer Licensee&apos;s copy of the Software together with its&#xA;Documentation on a permanent basis, so long as Licensee notifies Pramati as to the name and address of the&#xA;recipient of Licensee&apos;s copy and that such recipient agrees in writing to be bound by the terms and conditions&#xA;of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(h)&#x9;Results of benchmark or other performance tests run on the Software may not be disclosed to any third&#xA;party without Pramati&apos;s prior written consent.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(i)&#x9;The Software contains software programs written in Java. The Software is not fault-tolerant and is not&#xA;designed, manufactured or intended for use or resale in the on-line control, design, construction, operation or&#xA;maintenance of any nuclear facilities, aircraft navigation or communication systems, air traffic control, direct&#xA;life support machines, or weapons systems, in which the failure of the Software could lead directly to death,&#xA;personal injury, or severe physical or environmental damage (&quot;High Risk Activities&quot;). Pramati and its suppliers&#xA;specifically disclaim any express or implied warranty of fitness for High Risk Activities. Licensee agrees that it&#xA;is not licensed to use the Software for High Risk Activities and that failure to comply with this section will result&#xA;in immediate termination of this Agreement without refund.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;(j)&#x9;Third party software products supplied with the Software are provided to Licensee subject to such third&#xA;party&apos;s license agreement with Pramati, the terms of which may change from time to time. The Cloudscape&#xA;software products may only be used as a part of Pramati&apos;s development Software. The Cloudscape software&#xA;products may only be used on the operating system platforms on which Informix has made the Cloudscape&#xA;software generally commercially available. Licensee may not copy, distribute, or otherwise deploy the&#xA;Cloudscape software products or any other programs developed using such Cloudscape software. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;GENERAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;5. COPYRIGHT AND OWNERSHIP. Title, ownership rights, and all intellectual property rights in and to the&#xA;Software and Documentation including all copies thereof, and all rights therein including, but not limited to, all&#xA;trade secrets, trademarks, patents, copyrights, trade secrets and moral rights shall remain the sole and&#xA;exclusive property of Pramati and/or its licensors. Licensee acknowledges that the Software contains valuable&#xA;confidential information and trade secrets of Pramati and/or its licensors. No title or ownership to the Software&#xA;or Documentation or any part or modification thereof is transferred to Licensee. Software is protected by&#xA;copyright laws and international treaty provisions. Licensee shall not remove or alter Pramati&apos;s or any third&#xA;party&apos; s ownership, trademark, copyright, or other proprietary notices on the Software or Documentation.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;5.1 Pramati acknowledges that Software contains third-party software as listed in the attached files.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;5.2 Licensee acknowledges that Software contains software from third-party and agrees to abide by the&#xA;third-party agreements attached hereto. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;6. U.S. GOVERNMENT RIGHTS. If the Software or its Documentation is acquired by or on behalf of the United&#xA;States Government, the United States Government agrees that such Software and Documentation is&#xA;&quot;commercial computer software&quot; or &quot;commercial computer software documentation&quot; and that use,&#xA;modification, duplication and disclosure of the Software and its Documentation by the United States&#xA;Government is subject to restrictions set forth in this Agreement or in a written agreement to the contrary&#xA;specifying the United States Government&apos;s right to use the Software and its Documentation, pursuant to FAR&#xA;§ 12.212(a) and/or DFARS § 227.7202-1(a), as applicable. Pramati reserves all unpublished rights under U.S.&#xA;copyright laws.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;7. TERM OF LICENSE. Either party may terminate this Agreement if the other party materially breaches any of&#xA;its obligations hereunder and fails to cure such breach within thirty (30) days after written notice. Upon&#xA;termination, all rights granted to Licensee hereunder shall terminate and Licensee shall cease using the&#xA;Software, and within five (5) days of termination Licensee shall destroy or return to Pramati all copies of the&#xA;Software and its Documentation in any form. Upon request, Licensee shall certify that all copies of the&#xA;Software have been destroyed. Termination of this Agreement will not affect any provisions relating to the&#xA;payment of amounts due, limiting or disclaiming Pramati&apos;s liability, confidentiality, and ownership of copyrights&#xA;and other intellectual property of Pramati including, but not limited to, the Software and Documentation, which&#xA;provisions will survive termination of this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;8. CONFIDENTIALITY.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;8.1 Definition. Licensee agrees that information disclosed to it by Pramati including, but not limited to,&#xA;information learned or developed using the Software or Documentation, or that relates to its products, designs,&#xA;research, development, know-how, or third party confidential information, will be considered and referred to &#xA;collectively in this Agreement as &quot;Confidential Information.&quot; Confidential Information, however, does not include&#xA;information that 1) is now or subsequently becomes generally available to the public through no fault or breach&#xA;on the part of Licensee; 2) Licensee can demonstrate to have had rightfully in its possession prior to&#xA;disclosure by Pramati of such Confidential Information; 3) is independently developed by Licensee without the&#xA;use of any Confidential Information, the Software or Documentation of Pramati; or 4) Licensee rightfully obtains&#xA;from a third party who has the right to transfer or disclose it.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;8.2 Nondisclosure and Nonuse of Confidential Information. Except as otherwise set forth in this Agreement,&#xA;Licensee agrees that it will not disclosure, publish, or disseminate Confidential Information of Pramati to&#xA;anyone other than those of its employees with a demonstrated need to know, and Licensee agrees to take all&#xA;reasonable precautions to prevent any unauthorized use, disclosure, publication, or dissemination of&#xA;Confidential Information. Licensee agrees to use any Confidential Information disclosed to it solely for the&#xA;purposes contemplated by this Agreement and not otherwise for its own or any third party&apos;s benefit without the&#xA;prior written approval of an authorized representative of Pramati in each instance. All Confidential Information&#xA;remains the property of Pramati. Licensee shall enter into appropriate agreements, if Licensee has not already&#xA;done so, to protect the Confidential Information. Licensee shall not use Confidential Information at any time for&#xA;any purpose other than as authorized by Pramati.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;9. LIMITED WARRANTY. For a period of thirty (30) days from the date of Licensee&apos;s receipt of the Software,&#xA;Pramati warrants that the Software, when properly installed and used with the equipment configuration and in&#xA;the operating environment specified by Pramati, will operate in all material respects in conformity with its&#xA;Documentation, and the Software media shall be free of defects. Pramati warrants that Software telephone&#xA;support and training services (&quot;Related Service(s)&quot;) will be performed by qualified personnel in a professional&#xA;manner. In the event of non-conforming Software or Related Service(s), or if the media is defective, Licensee&apos;s&#xA;sole remedy and Pramati&apos;s exclusive liability shall be, as applicable and at Pramati&apos;s option, replacement of&#xA;the affected Software or media, or re-performance of the Related Service(s) at no additional charge, or a refund&#xA;of the fees paid for the affected Software or Related Service(s). EVALUATION SOFTWARE AND ANY THIRD&#xA;PARTY SOFTWARE ARE PROVIDED TO LICENSEE &quot;AS IS&quot; WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY, EXPRESS OR&#xA;IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE. PRAMATI DISCLAIMS ALL OTHER WARRANTIES AND&#xA;CONDITIONS, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION&#xA;THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND&#xA;WHETHER ARISING BY STATUTE OR IN LAW OR AS A RESULT OF A COURSE OF DEALING OR&#xA;USAGE OF TRADE, WITH RESPECT TO THE SOFTWARE, ITS DOCUMENTATION, SUPPORT OR OTHER&#xA;SERVICES RELATED TO THE SOFTWARE. NO WARRANTY IS MADE REGARDING THE RESULTS OF&#xA;THE SOFTWARE OR RELATED SERVICES OR THAT ALL ERRORS IN THE SOFTWARE WILL BE&#xA;CORRECTED, OR THAT THE SOFTWARE&apos;S FUNCTIONALITY WILL MEET LICENSEE&apos;S REQUIREMENTS.&#xA;LICENSEE ACKNOWLEDGES LICENSEE&apos;S RESPONSIBILITY TO (i) REGULARLY BACK UP DATA&#xA;MAINTAINED ON ANY COMPUTER SYSTEM USING THE SOFTWARE AND (ii) ADEQUATELY TEST&#xA;PRIOR TO DEPLOYMENT EACH PRODUCTION VERSION OF THE SOFTWARE IN A CONFIGURATION&#xA;WHICH REASONABLY SIMULATES LICENSEE&apos;S PLANNED DEPLOYMENT OR PRODUCTION&#xA;ENVIRONMENT. This limited warranty gives Licensee specific legal rights. Licensee may have other rights that&#xA;vary among jurisdictions. Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of implied conditions or warranties,&#xA;statutory or otherwise, so the above exclusions may not apply to Licensee.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;10. LIMITATIONS ON LIABILITY. PRAMATI&apos;S LICENSORS SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR DIRECT DAMAGES&#xA;OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER UNDER THIS AGREEMENT. UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL&#xA;PRAMATI, ITS SUBSIDIARIES OR ANY OF ITS LICENSORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOSS OR&#xA;INACCURACY OF DATA, LOSS OF PROFITS OR INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL&#xA;OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES, EVEN IF SUCH PARTY HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF&#xA;SUCH DAMAGES. TOTAL LIABILITY, IF ANY, ARISING OUT OF THIS AGREEMENT OR LICENSEE&apos;S USE&#xA;OF THE SOFTWARE OR RELATED SERVICES SHALL EXCEED THE FEES PAID BY LICENSEE FOR THE&#xA;AFFECTED SOFTWARE OR RELATED SERVICE(S) GIVING RISE TO THE CLAIM. THE FOREGOING&#xA;RESTRICTIONS, DISCLAIMERS AND LIMITATIONS SHALL REMAIN IN FORCE EVEN IN THE EVENT OF A&#xA;FUNDAMENTAL BREACH BY PRAMATI OR A BREACH BY PRAMATI OF A CONDITION OR&#xA;FUNDAMENTAL TERM HEREUNDER. Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion or limitation of indirect,&#xA;special, incidental, consequential or exemplary damages or the limitation of liability to specified amounts, so&#xA;the above limitations or exclusions may not apply to Licensee. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;10.1 Licensee acknowledges that Pramati has no knowledge of, or control over, the installation or use of the&#xA;Software by Licensee. Licensee agrees to defend, indemnify and hold Pramati harmless with respect to any&#xA;suit, claim or proceeding brought against Pramati alleging that installation or use by, or under authority of,&#xA;Licensee of the Software caused personal injury, property damage, or economic loss.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;11. GOVERNING LAW; COMPLETE AGREEMENT. This Agreement shall be construed and enforced in&#xA;accordance with the laws of the State of California, United States of America. The parties agree that venue for&#xA;any dispute under this Agreement shall be San Mateo County, California, U.S.A.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;12. AUDIT RIGHTS.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;12.1 Licensee shall keep accurate records of all activity with respect to use of the Software by Licensee,&#xA;including, without limitation, all Editions of Software used and the number of Named Users accessing the&#xA;Software or the number of CPUs. Licensee shall provide Pramati with summaries of such records upon&#xA;request. At any time during the term of this Agreement, Pramati shall have the right to audit Licensee&apos;s records&#xA;in order to verify that Licensee is limiting use of the Software in accordance with this Agreement. If any audit&#xA;reveals that Licensee is not limiting use of the Software in accordance with this Agreement, Licensee shall&#xA;pay Pramati any underpaid license fees at Pramati&apos;s then current rates within five days of notification of such&#xA;underpayment. If any audit reveals that Licensee has underpaid Pramati by an amount equal to or greater than&#xA;five percent of applicable license fees, Licensee shall also reimburse Pramati for the costs associated with the&#xA;audit.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;13. NOTICES. All notices or other communications required to be given under this Agreement shall be in&#xA;writing and delivered either personally or by mail via an internationally recognized governmental or private mail&#xA;service, certified, return receipt requested, postage prepaid, and addressed as provided in this Agreement or&#xA;as otherwise requested by the receiving party. Notices delivered personally shall be effective upon delivery and&#xA;notices delivered by mail shall be effective upon their receipt by the party to whom they are addressed.&#xA;Licensee shall address all correspondence regarding this Agreement to the Company Secretary of Pramati&#xA;Technologies (P) Ltd. at the Hyderabad, India Office whose address is available at www.pramati.com.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;14. ENTIRE AGREEMENT; MODIFICATIONS AND WAIVERS. This Agreement constitutes the full and entire&#xA;understanding and agreement between the parties with regard to the subjects hereof.  No term of this&#xA;Agreement may be modified except by a writing signed by an authorized representative of each of the parties.&#xA;A waiver by a party of its rights under this Agreement shall not be binding unless contained in a writing signed&#xA;by an authorized representative of the party waiving its rights. The non-enforcement or waiver of any provision&#xA;on one (1) occasion shall not constitute a waiver of such provision on any other occasions unless expressly so&#xA;agreed in writing. It is agreed that no use of trade or other regular practice or method of dealing between the&#xA;parties hereto shall be used to modify, interpret, supplement, or alter in any manner the terms of this&#xA;Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;15. SEVERABILITY. In the event that any provision of this Agreement is found invalid or unenforceable pursuant&#xA;to judicial decree or decision, the remainder of this Agreement shall remain valid and enforceable according to&#xA;its terms.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;16. FORCE MAJEURE. No party shall be responsible for any failure to perform due to unforeseen&#xA;circumstances or to causes beyond the party&apos;s reasonable control, including but not limited to acts of God,&#xA;war, riot, embargoes, acts of civil or military authorities, fire, floods, accidents, strikes, or shortages of&#xA;transportation, facilities, fuel, energy, labor, or materials. In the event of any such delay, a party may defer any&#xA;delivery dates for a period equal to the time of such delay. Notwithstanding the foregoing, if a party is in default&#xA;under this Section for more than fifteen (15) days, the non-defaulting party may terminate this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;17. ARBITRATION. Any controversy or claim arising out of or relating to this Agreement, or the breach thereof&#xA;shall be settled by binding arbitration in the County of San Mateo, California, administered by the American&#xA;Arbitration Association in accordance with its then current Commercial Arbitration Rules, and judgment on the&#xA;award rendered by the arbitrator may be entered in any court having jurisdiction thereof. The arbitrator may&#xA;award monetary damages, punitive damages, injunctive relief, rescission, restitution, costs and attorneys&apos;&#xA;fees. The arbitration award shall be final and binding regardless of whether one of the parties fails or refuses to&#xA;participate in the arbitration. The arbitrator shall not have the power to amend this Agreement in any respect.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;18. ATTORNEYS&apos; FEES. In the event of any dispute with respect to this Agreement, the prevailing party shall&#xA;be entitled to reasonable attorneys&apos; fees and other costs and expenses incurred in resolving such dispute.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;19. TAXES. Unless otherwise agreed between Consultant and Company, Consultant and Company shall each&#xA;have sole responsibility for collecting, reporting, and/or paying all income, sales, excise, property, value-added&#xA;tax, and other taxes imposed by any governmental authority as they pertain to Consultant&apos;s and Company&apos;s&#xA;respective duties, obligations, and performance hereunder.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20. DEFINITIONS.&#xA;&#xA;As used herein, the terms set forth below shall have the following respective meanings:&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.1 &quot;Documentation&quot; means the publications prepared and delivered to Licensee by Pramati that accompanies&#xA;the Software, such as reference, user, installation, systems administrator and technical guides. &#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.2 &quot;CPU&quot; means each central processing unit designated for use on a specific computing device.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.3 &quot;Software&quot; shall mean the machine readable object code, delivered by Pramati, to Licensee and may&#xA;include software licensed from third parties, together with other software and/or other products subsequently&#xA;delivered to Licensee by Pramati and all updates and upgrades of the same provided to Licensee by Pramati&#xA;and/or its suppliers. Software includes &quot;Server Software&quot; including current release(s) of Pramati Server and&#xA;Pramati Message Server and &quot;Studio Software&quot; including current release(s) of Pramati Studio and &quot;Plugin&#xA;Software&quot;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.4 &quot;Pramati&quot; shall mean Pramati Technologies (P) Limited, as incorporated in the State of Andhra Pradesh,&#xA;India, under Companies Act, 1956, whose address can be found at Pramati&apos;s website at www.pramati.com.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.5 &quot;Licensee&quot; shall mean the entity or individual, either on the individual&apos; s behalf or on behalf of the entity that&#xA;individual represents, who installs the Software or otherwise agrees to be bound by the terms and conditions&#xA;contained in this Agreement. Further, each individual representing an entity represents and warrants that&#xA;he/she has the authority to bind the entity to this Agreement.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.6 &quot;Named Users&quot; shall mean an individual or individuals employed by Licensee who is/are authorized to use&#xA;the software. The number of licenses for the Program must equal the total number of Named Users.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.7 &quot;Application&quot; shall mean machine-readable object code provided by &quot;Application Provider&quot; to Licensee&#xA;which may be deployed on Software.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;20.8 &quot;Edition&quot; shall mean either the Standard Edition or the Enterprise Edition of the Software.  The Standard&#xA;Edition does not allow use of certain features available in the Enterprise Edition.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;BY CLICKING THE &quot;ACCEPT&quot; BUTTON OR CHECKING THE &quot;ACCEPT&quot; CHECK-BOX DURING&#xA;INSTALLATION OF THE SOFTWARE, LICENSEE IS AGREEING TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND&#xA;CONDITIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT.&#xA;'/>
        <property name='df_LT.copyright' value='Copyright © 2008 Pramati Technologies. All Rights Reserved.'/>
        <property name='df_LT.featureName' value='Pramati Server 6.0 Plugin'/>
        <property name='df_LT.description' value='Pramati Server Plugin Feature 2.0.0 : Supported server versions 4.1, 5.0 and 6.0'/>
        <property name='df_LT.providerName' value='Pramati Technologies'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='2'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.group' version='2.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.localization' name='df_LT' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='2'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.jst.server' range='[2.0.0,2.0.0]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.jar' range='[2.0.0,2.0.0]'>
          <filter>
            (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
          </filter>
        </required>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='%25licenseURL' url='%25licenseURL'>
          %license
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        %copyright
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='com.pramati.jst.server' version='1.0.1' singleton='false'>
      <update id='com.pramati.jst.server' range='[0.0.0,1.0.1)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='1'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.partial.iu' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.jst.server' version='1.0.1'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='com.pramati.jst.server' version='1.0.1'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='com.pramati.jst.server' version='1.0.1'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: com.pramati.jst.server&#xA;Bundle-Version: 1.0.1&#xA;
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='com.pramati.jst.server' version='2.0.0' singleton='false'>
      <update id='com.pramati.jst.server' range='[0.0.0,2.0.0)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='1'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.partial.iu' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.jst.server' version='2.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='com.pramati.jst.server' version='2.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='com.pramati.jst.server' version='2.0.0'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: com.pramati.jst.server&#xA;Bundle-Version: 2.0.0&#xA;
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='http://www.pramati.com/downloads/eclipse/updates/site.xml.Pramati Server Adapter' version='1.0.0.7D51cL2qnh'>
      <properties size='2'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='Pramati Server Adapter'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.category' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='1'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='http://www.pramati.com/downloads/eclipse/updates/site.xml.Pramati Server Adapter' version='1.0.0.7D51cL2qnh'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='4'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.group' range='[2.1.0,2.1.0]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.group' range='[2.2.0,2.2.0]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.group' range='[1.0.1,1.0.1]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.eclipse.feature.feature.group' range='[2.0.0,2.0.0]'/>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
    </unit>
    <unit id='com.pramati.jst.server' version='2.1.0' singleton='false'>
      <update id='com.pramati.jst.server' range='[0.0.0,2.1.0)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='1'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.partial.iu' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.jst.server' version='2.1.0'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='com.pramati.jst.server' version='2.1.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='com.pramati.jst.server' version='2.1.0'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: com.pramati.jst.server&#xA;Bundle-Version: 2.1.0&#xA;
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='com.pramati.jst.server' version='2.2.0' singleton='false'>
      <update id='com.pramati.jst.server' range='[0.0.0,2.2.0)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='1'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.partial.iu' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='com.pramati.jst.server' version='2.2.0'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='com.pramati.jst.server' version='2.2.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='com.pramati.jst.server' version='2.2.0'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: com.pramati.jst.server&#xA;Bundle-Version: 2.2.0&#xA;
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
  </units>
</repository>
